<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>elizaOS Council Briefings</title>
    <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge</link>
    <description>Strategic briefings and deliberation items for elizaOS leadership</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 02:24:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/rss/council.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-21</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-21.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-21.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The Council stands at a launch threshold: Cloud MVP and streaming capabilities are poised to ship, but community trust is under strain from migration confusion, price anxiety, and active scam pressure—requiring disciplined execution and clearer doctrine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud MVP Launch Readiness (Streaming + Release Discipline):&lt;/strong&gt; Operational posture indicates imminent Cloud MVP shipment with streaming enabled (v1.7.0), but coordination risk remains around release sequencing and low visible day-to-day GitHub throughput on the l...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration, Liquidity Friction, and Utility Credibility:&lt;/strong&gt; Migration remains confusing and emotionally charged, amplified by ai16z price anomalies and liquidity fragmentation across chains; Council must align migration doctrine, support pathways for edge wall...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Posture and Community Trust Under Active Scam Pressure:&lt;/strong&gt; Scam activity and impersonation risk are actively harming support channels, and token-migration confusion increases the attack surface; Council must reinforce operational security, official comms, and...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-20</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-20.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-20.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; All vectors converge on shipping Cloud streaming with release-discipline (monorepo → plugin → cloud-v2) while restoring trust via clear migration guidance amid visible community frustration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Streaming: Launch Readiness &amp; Release Discipline:&lt;/strong&gt; Streaming is functionally working in simple flows, but the release train has critical dependencies (monorepo release, elizacloud-plugin merge, cloud-v2 core bump) plus operational blockers (NPM token ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration: Trust, Support Integrity, and Exchange Confusion:&lt;/strong&gt; The Feb 4, 2026 deadline is understood by some but still confusing in practice (“0 eligible”, exchange snapshot discrepancies), and sentiment is deteriorating. Trust-through-shipping now depends as mu...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Experience: Plugin Reliability, EVM Readiness, and Ecosystem Observability:&lt;/strong&gt; Builders are probing whether plugin-evm is truly supported while Starknet integration and provider performance changes highlight API churn and type friction. The knowledge repository and new GitHub an...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-19</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-19.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-19.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Council attention is split between execution excellence in the runtime (streaming + provider performance hardening) and a rising legitimacy risk from token migration confusion and community distrust that threatens the Cloud launch narrative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Runtime Reliability: Streaming &amp; Provider Performance Contracts:&lt;/strong&gt; Core shipped a major streaming enhancement (merged PR #6212), while an open refactor (PR #6263) proposes parallel provider execution with timeouts—signaling a push toward reliability but exposing an u...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration &amp; Exchange Coordination: Trust Incident Containment:&lt;/strong&gt; Migration confusion across exchanges (e.g., Bithumb vs Kraken handling) and user reports of a "disastrous" swap are creating a reputational gravity well; without crisp, multilingual guidance and verif...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer-First Delivery: Plugin Integration Friction &amp; Documentation Debt:&lt;/strong&gt; Builders are hitting friction integrating new plugins (Starknet type mismatches, missing handlers, unclear CLI flows) while major ecosystem PRs (Discord plugin) sit large and stale; combined with an o...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-18</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-18.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-18.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The council’s immediate leverage point is restoring trust through crisp token-migration communications and security posture while unblocking Cloud/streaming and plugin shipping decisions that prove production readiness ahead of exchange momentum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Trust, Exchange Coordination, and Safety Posture:&lt;/strong&gt; Migration remains technically possible on Solana, but exchange-specific handling (notably Bithumb vs Kraken) is producing confusion and reputational drag, compounded by community anxiety about migrati...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Streaming &amp; Messaging Plugins: Shipping Discipline Under Scale:&lt;/strong&gt; Streaming is working for simple messages/actions across cloud and monorepo, but Actions UI rendering still breaks the experience; meanwhile a massive Discord plugin PR is waiting to merge, raising qua...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Trust Through DX: Docs, Plugins, and Onboarding Clarity:&lt;/strong&gt; Builders are hitting friction in extending actions and local DB setup, while GitHub shows a surge in UX/backlog definition; the Council must convert this signal into a coherent, reliability-first onbo...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-17</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-17.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-17.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; As Kraken listing and migration chatter peak, the Council’s critical priority is preserving trust by hardening the token-migration surface area (security + exchange coordination) while simultaneously proving Cloud readiness through visible reliability wins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration &amp; Exchange-Edge Trust (Kraken/Bithumb + Site Security):&lt;/strong&gt; The migration narrative is now the public face of ElizaOS: Kraken listing (Dec 19) increases scrutiny while unresolved exchange delays and a reported migration-site compromise risk reputational damage...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Launch Readiness (Streaming UX, Auth, and Create→Publish→Monetize Loop):&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud capability is advancing (integrations, end-to-end business cycle vision), but the Council must decide what 'launch' means: a hardened minimal path with impeccable UX, or a broader platform debut...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Experience &amp; Reliability Flywheel (DB Migrations, PR Proof, AI-Assisted Workflow):&lt;/strong&gt; Developer trust is trending upward via heavy refactors, tests, and SQL/migration fixes, but field reports still show friction (Postgres permissions/migrations, foreign key failures). The Council must ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-16</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-16.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-16.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Trust is being stress-tested by token migration delays (notably Bithumb) and an alleged migration-site compromise, making incident response and clear communications the highest-leverage actions for execution excellence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Reliability &amp; Security Posture:&lt;/strong&gt; Community pressure is escalating around CEX-held migration delays and an alleged phishing/compromise of the migration site; both directly threaten the monthly directive of high-success migration and d...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Launch Trajectory (Create → Publish → Monetize → Promote):&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud progress is strong with a full business-cycle vision and new integrations/partners, but the Council must decide how to stage-access, message the value, and avoid overextending reliability during...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Framework Stability &amp; Developer Trust (DX, Testing Discipline, Data Integrity):&lt;/strong&gt; Recent GitHub momentum shows heavy refactors, dependency alignment, and Cloud-first CLI improvements, while Discord surfaces ongoing runtime friction (plugin registration errors, DB constraints) and a...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-15</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-15.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-15.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud commercialization systems (create→publish→monetize→promote) are converging toward launch, but near-term trust hinges on resolving token migration UX/documentation gaps and tightening operational safety signals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Launch Readiness &amp; Growth Loop Integrity:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud development reports strong momentum with an end-to-end business loop plus SEO/ads/social integrations, indicating a shift from tooling to ecosystem commerce. Council must decide what "launch" me...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration UX, Hardware Wallet Visibility, and Documentation Debt:&lt;/strong&gt; Token migration friction is surfacing in user reports, particularly Ledger visibility and connection pathways, creating a direct threat to the monthly directive's "high success rate" requirement. The ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reliability &amp; Safety Signals: Plugin Configuration, API Waste, and Scam Surface Area:&lt;/strong&gt; Developer friction continues via runtime errors (TEXT_LARGE tied to missing inference plugins), while operational risks include excessive Twitter-agent API calls and active scam/spam attempts in commu...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-14</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-14.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-14.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Developer trust was stressed by a “fails-on-hello” onboarding path (TEXT_LARGE + plugin install friction), signaling that Cloud/CLI defaults and documentation must eliminate inference-provider misconfiguration as we push toward launch readiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Onboarding Reliability (Inference Plugin + Updates):&lt;/strong&gt; A coder encountered TEXT_LARGE errors even on minimal prompts, traced to missing inference plugin registration; subsequent plugin installation issues were attributed to outdated packages, reinforcing ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Launch Readiness (CLI Defaults + Key Management):&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud is being positioned as the default AI provider in the CLI and a large Cloud integration PR is in flight; community questions indicate confusion about whether provider keys must be wired into Clo...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Trust &amp; Exchange Friction (Bithumb / Transparency):&lt;/strong&gt; Migration remains a reputational risk vector, with Korean users reporting blocking issues on Bithumb and community speculation about burn/sell mechanics; transparency steps exist but require clearer, ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-13</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-13.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-13.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Council attention should converge on trust restoration: a critical secrets-exfiltration vulnerability and persistent token migration friction are colliding with Cloud launch ambitions, making “secure-by-default + clear comms” the immediate path to execution excellence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Hardening: Secrets, Auth, and Production Defaults:&lt;/strong&gt; A critical vulnerability enabled unauthenticated API access to extract agent secrets due to environment variables being written into unencrypted settings; it was introduced in v1.6.4 and fixed in v1.6...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Reliability and Transparency (Bithumb + Narrative Risk):&lt;/strong&gt; Korean users report significant migration failures on Bithumb, creating prolonged frustration and price-related anxiety; unanswered questions about burns and supply handling persist. Execution excelle...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud &amp; DX Launch Readiness: CLI Integration, Stability, and Signal-to-Noise:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud integration work is accelerating (large PRs for Cloud provider defaults and CLI login/provisioning), while stability issues persist across the monorepo (TypeScript breakages, plugin-sql DB const...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-12</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-12.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-12.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Core technical foundation improvements and fixes for elizaOS are advancing while token migration issues threaten user trust and engagement with the ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Crisis Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Korean users are experiencing significant migration problems with Bithumb exchange, creating trust issues and frustration, while the continuous price decline of ELIZA raises questions about the migrat...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Foundation Strengthening:&lt;/strong&gt; The development team is making significant progress on core infrastructure with monorepo fixes, database optimizations, and standardization efforts, but performance bottlenecks and security concerns r...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Launch Strategy:&lt;/strong&gt; The ecosystem has multiple projects advancing toward launch, including Babylon as a web browser game and elizaOS Cloud integration, but clarity on timelines and feature sets remains limited....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-11</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-11.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-11.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Critical security vulnerability discovered in elizaOS server requiring immediate remediation to protect agent secrets and user data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Infrastructure Overhaul:&lt;/strong&gt; A critical security vulnerability was discovered allowing unauthorized access to agent secrets through API endpoints, requiring immediate fixes to encryption methods and authentication protocols....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cross-Chain Integration Strategy:&lt;/strong&gt; Development of Jeju testnet with cross-chain liquidity pools enables using elizaOS tokens as gas across multiple chains without bridging, opening new ecosystem expansion possibilities....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plugin System Stability:&lt;/strong&gt; Multiple users reported foreign key constraint errors with database plugins, highlighting the need for improved migration paths and stability in the plugin ecosystem....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-10</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-10.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-10.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Community concern over token migration and platform stability rising as technical teams prioritize codebase quality and next-generation features over immediate user-facing functionality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Trust &amp; Token Economics:&lt;/strong&gt; The AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration has sparked significant community frustration due to the sudden snapshot, supply increase, and declining token price, undermining confidence in the project's econo...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Delivery &amp; Timeline Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Multiple core products (ElizaOS Cloud, Babylon, Jeju) are behind communicated schedules, with the development team focused on infrastructure and technical debt rather than user-facing features, creati...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agent Architecture &amp; Capability Limitations:&lt;/strong&gt; Current agent infrastructure faces critical limitations in composability, uptime guarantees, and long-term accessibility that conflict with our mission of creating reliable 24/7 autonomous agents for ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-09</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-09.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-09.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The elizaOS.ai website security breach represents a critical vulnerability in our infrastructure that requires immediate attention to maintain trust and protect our community as we scale agent activity and prepare for v2 launch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Infrastructure Resilience:&lt;/strong&gt; The elizaOS.ai website was compromised with an XMR cryptocurrency miner, exposing vulnerabilities in our technical infrastructure that could impede our goal of attracting and retaining users through 2...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agent Performance Optimization:&lt;/strong&gt; Current Twitter agent limitations and discussions around streaming functionality indicate significant bottlenecks in our agent ecosystem that may prevent us from delivering the 24/7 activity required ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Confidence &amp; Tokenomics:&lt;/strong&gt; The continuous decline in token value and questions about exchange listings highlight community concerns about project sustainability, potentially undermining our ability to attract users to auto.fun ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-08</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-08.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-08.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Development efforts are advancing the technical foundation for elizaOS v2 while token migration issues continue to challenge user experience and community sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Challenges:&lt;/strong&gt; The ai16z to ElizaOS token migration is creating friction in the user experience, with confusion over eligibility, safety concerns, and exchange availability potentially impacting adoption momentum....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Architecture Evolution:&lt;/strong&gt; Core development teams are advancing several significant architectural improvements simultaneously, including parallel action execution, JWT authentication, and server optimization, which collectively...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Growth Strategy:&lt;/strong&gt; While technical development advances, there are signs of untapped developer interest and opportunities to better structure community onboarding and engagement, particularly as we prepare for auto.fun ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-07</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-07.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-07.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Technical advancements in elizaOS v2 development are accelerating with parallel action execution implementation and ElizaCloud integration, while token migration issues continue to require community support resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS v2 Technical Optimization:&lt;/strong&gt; The core development team is advancing parallel action execution in v2 and has successfully implemented ElizaCloud as the default AI provider in CLI, both critical steps toward production-ready elizaO...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration &amp; Community Management:&lt;/strong&gt; The AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration continues to cause confusion among users, requiring significant support resources and clear communication to maintain community trust during this transition....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Integration &amp; Ecosystem Expansion:&lt;/strong&gt; The elizaOS ecosystem is expanding with ElizaCloud, decentralized OTC desk, and potential Babylon integration, requiring strategic decisions about how these components connect and create value for use...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-06</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-06.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-06.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The engineering team is making significant progress on unified streaming support across plugins while simultaneously addressing token migration challenges and security concerns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Streaming Support Implementation:&lt;/strong&gt; The team is actively developing unified streaming support across plugins, starting with plugin-openrouter before extending to plugin-openai and plugin-anthropic, representing a critical technical mile...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration &amp; Security:&lt;/strong&gt; The community is experiencing challenges with the AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration, while simultaneously facing increased security threats from scammers targeting users during this transition period....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Experience Enhancement:&lt;/strong&gt; Recent work indicates a need to improve the developer experience for elizaOS, with focus areas including streamlining agent setup and addressing technical issues like plugin behavior and directory man...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-05</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-05.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-05.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The ecosystem faces a critical dual challenge between token migration issues impacting Korean exchanges and significant developer experience barriers in the elizaOS framework that threaten to undermine adoption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Crisis:&lt;/strong&gt; The unilateral snapshot taken on November 11, 2025, has caused significant migration problems for users on Korean exchanges, with the Digital Asset eXchange Alliance (DAXA) placing AI16Z under an 'Inv...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Experience Crisis:&lt;/strong&gt; Core developers have identified severe usability issues with the elizaOS framework, requiring excessive boilerplate code and complex setup even for basic 'hello world' agents, which threatens to under...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Auto.fun Go-to-Market Strategy:&lt;/strong&gt; With upcoming launches including Babylon platform, ElizaCloud, and Otako in development, and competitive pressure from Chinese model providers and Anthropic's growth, we need to determine the most eff...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-04</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-04.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-04.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The elizaOS ecosystem faces critical token migration issues amid parallel technical advances in authentication, user management, and server optimization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Challenges:&lt;/strong&gt; The ai16z to elizaOS token migration is experiencing significant friction with users confused about the process, scammers exploiting the situation, and major exchanges pausing trading while evaluating...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Architecture Evolution:&lt;/strong&gt; Development efforts are advancing on multiple fronts with significant PRs focused on authentication systems, API unification, and server optimization, all crucial for supporting the auto.fun launch an...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product-Market Alignment:&lt;/strong&gt; With ongoing negotiations for social media restoration, competition from former team members' projects, and a need to differentiate through user-centric features, the project must clarify its market p...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-03</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-03.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-03.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Core development teams are advancing critical technical infrastructure improvements for elizaOS v2 while navigating ongoing token migration challenges that impact community sentiment and exchange relationships.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Architecture Enhancements:&lt;/strong&gt; Development efforts are focused on critical improvements to plugin memory architecture, authentication, and streaming capabilities, with discussions about cost-effective scaling through multi-agent se...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaCloud Marketplace Strategy:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussions around ElizaCloud's business model suggest implementing a marketplace similar to Salesforce AppExchange or Apple App Store with revenue sharing from third-party developers and standardized...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration and Exchange Relations:&lt;/strong&gt; The ongoing migration from AI16Z to ElizaOS tokens with a 6:1 conversion ratio is creating challenges as exchanges like Kraken pause trading while evaluating support for the migration, affecting user ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-02</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-02.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-02.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The elizaOS ecosystem shows significant technical refinement and infrastructure optimization alongside community challenges in token migration and Discord plugin functionality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Infrastructure Enhancement:&lt;/strong&gt; Core technical improvements focusing on server optimization, reliability patterns, and user interface refinements indicate progress toward a production-ready elizaOS v2, though community-facing tools ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Business Model Evolution:&lt;/strong&gt; Community discussions around AI agent monetization strategies, particularly in lead generation and brand-specific agents, present opportunities to diversify elizaOS revenue streams and drive growth fo...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Experience Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Community members are experiencing token migration challenges and technical issues with elizaOS tools, requiring improved documentation, support processes, and communication to maintain momentum and e...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
