<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>elizaOS Council Briefings</title>
    <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge</link>
    <description>Strategic briefings and deliberation items for elizaOS leadership</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 02:40:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/rss/council.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-28</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-28.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-28.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Operational momentum bifurcated: public trust friction intensified around snapshot-based token migration while core engineering surfaced a bold Jeju/Eliza Cloud future—yet daily GitHub throughput dipped to near-idle, risking execution credibility at month-end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Clarity &amp; Trust Repair:&lt;/strong&gt; Snapshot-locked migration policy is generating repeated user failure modes ("max amount reached" / "0 eligible") and compounding reputational damage during a major price drawdown. The Council must dec...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Reliability &amp; Developer Experience Gaps:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud is live and attracting projects, but edge-case failures (agent naming, deployment credentials, UI multistep streaming) are breaking the “seamless UX” promise. The Council should prioritize a sma...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jeju Distributed Cloud Trajectory vs. Month-End Execution Risk:&lt;/strong&gt; Jeju’s vision (TEE-secured, proof-of-cloud, sharded KMS, serverless SQLite) is strategically aligned with cross-chain, unstoppable agents—but the immediate signal shows low day-to-day repo activity an...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-27</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-27.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-27.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; With ElizaOS Cloud now launched, the Council’s priority is to convert early builder traction into trust by rapidly eliminating login/deploy regressions and clarifying token/Jeju alignment before market narrative fractures further.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Launch: Stabilization and First-Impression Reliability:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud has launched and builders are deploying agents, but early friction (login errors, username-null deploy failures, file upload constraints) threatens the developer-first narrative; execution excel...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Fallout: Trust, Liquidity Fragmentation, and Exchange Risk:&lt;/strong&gt; Migration mechanics (snapshot eligibility, wallet constraints) and liquidity fragmentation are driving confusion and reputational drag, while delisting fears create time pressure; we need a single aut...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identity, Streaming, and Core Reliability: The DX Trust Layer:&lt;/strong&gt; Multiple signals point to “trust layer” gaps—broken streaming due to dependency mismatch, need for unified SSO, and bun-only constraints—indicating that developer experience now depends on rigorous in...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-26</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-26.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-26.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The program is absorbing fallout from a confusing token migration (eligibility, scams, exchange risk) while needing to re-anchor legitimacy by making Cloud the tangible reliability-and-revenue engine the market can understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Integrity + Exchange Risk Containment:&lt;/strong&gt; Community trust is being eroded by migration eligibility constraints (snapshot + original wallet), perceived unfairness, and active scam attempts; Korean exchange delisting risk introduces a hard near...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud as the Tokenomics Engine + Strategic User Acquisition:&lt;/strong&gt; Eliza Cloud is positioned as the first credible value-accrual mechanism (revenue-funded buybacks), and a proposed Babylon points-game integration could migrate ~350,000 users—if the Council can ensure...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Execution Excellence Signal: Docs, Support Reliability, and Visible Shipping Cadence:&lt;/strong&gt; Despite strong December engineering output, the latest daily GitHub signal shows a momentary stall (0 PRs/issues Dec 25–26), while user-facing pain (outdated docs, migration bot misinformation, CI bil...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-25</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-25.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-25.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Council attention converges on trust repair: clarifying token value accrual and migration safety while hardening Cloud beta reliability and documentation to sustain developer confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Trust, Value Accrual, and Migration Safety:&lt;/strong&gt; Community sentiment is dominated by token drawdown anxiety and unclear value accrual narratives; the team’s message is that Cloud revenue (not yield) funds buybacks and future utility arrives with Jej...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Beta Readiness &amp; Developer Onboarding:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud is in beta onboarding with a January ramp planned; near-term product constraints (50MB uploads, no custom model hosting yet) and promised roadmap items (custom model hosting next week) must be d...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reliability &amp; DX Debt: Docs, CI Integrity, and Chat Isolation Bugs:&lt;/strong&gt; Operational signals show classic trust erosion vectors: outdated monorepo docs, CI failures due to billing, and UI/chat behavior issues (conversation duplication and default conversation selection) th...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-24</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-24.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-24.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS Cloud has entered beta and must now be hardened into a reliable, developer-first agent registration and monetization corridor ahead of the January ramp and the mid-February EthDenver onboarding push.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eliza Cloud Beta → January Ramp Readiness:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud beta is live with ecosystem builders being onboarded for production feedback, and leadership is positioning Cloud as the default registry/registration surface before EthDenver. The Council must ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Framework Reliability: Unified Messaging, Streaming, and Plugin Hygiene:&lt;/strong&gt; Core developers report fixes to streaming in cloud build mode and Discord plugin issues, while standardizing message handling across plugins remains a key dependency for stability and composability. T...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trust &amp; Token Utility Narrative Under Market Stress:&lt;/strong&gt; Discord logs show continued community frustration around token drawdown and demands for visible utility; team messaging points to Cloud as the tokenomics engine, with prior mentions of buybacks and re...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-23</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-23.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-23.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Launch proximity for ElizaOS Cloud is colliding with rising community distrust (token utility confusion) and last-mile reliability/security issues, making “trust-through-shipping + clear documentation” the decisive battlefront.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Launch Readiness (Ship, Don’t Slip):&lt;/strong&gt; The org signals imminent Cloud/MVP shipping and positions Cloud as the flagship DX wedge; however, current public understanding is fragmentary and operational readiness signals (no PR movement in core...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Utility, Narrative, and Documentation (Trust Repair):&lt;/strong&gt; Community morale is being eroded by severe price drawdown and unresolved questions about token utility, audits, and migration edge cases; the logs repeatedly point to a communications failure where cr...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reliability &amp; Security Front (Plugins + Supply Chain):&lt;/strong&gt; Operational risk is concentrated in (1) a Starknet plugin BigInt parsing failure impacting real user flows, (2) a disclosed CVE-10 RCE in n8n mentioned by core-devs, and (3) reported CLI bloat (17GB) ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-22</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-22.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-22.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Council attention converges on ElizaOS Cloud MVP launch readiness (streaming + release choreography) while community trust is strained by migration confusion, liquidity gaps, and escalating scam pressure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud MVP Launch Readiness (Streaming + Release Choreography):&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud MVP is slated to ship imminently, with streaming support and a strict merge/release order spanning monorepo, cloud plugin, and cloud-v2; execution quality here directly determines developer trus...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Integrity, Liquidity Asymmetry, and Utility Signaling:&lt;/strong&gt; Migration confusion persists (snapshot eligibility, deadline, deprecated token pumping), compounded by chain liquidity differences; the Council must align messaging, support pathways, and near-term ut...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Posture: Scam Pressure vs. Trust Through Shipping:&lt;/strong&gt; Discord scam attempts are actively targeting users amid migration confusion; strengthening official communication authenticity and support routing is now a critical reliability feature, not a communit...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-21</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-21.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-21.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The Council stands at a launch threshold: Cloud MVP and streaming capabilities are poised to ship, but community trust is under strain from migration confusion, price anxiety, and active scam pressure—requiring disciplined execution and clearer doctrine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud MVP Launch Readiness (Streaming + Release Discipline):&lt;/strong&gt; Operational posture indicates imminent Cloud MVP shipment with streaming enabled (v1.7.0), but coordination risk remains around release sequencing and low visible day-to-day GitHub throughput on the l...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration, Liquidity Friction, and Utility Credibility:&lt;/strong&gt; Migration remains confusing and emotionally charged, amplified by ai16z price anomalies and liquidity fragmentation across chains; Council must align migration doctrine, support pathways for edge wall...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Posture and Community Trust Under Active Scam Pressure:&lt;/strong&gt; Scam activity and impersonation risk are actively harming support channels, and token-migration confusion increases the attack surface; Council must reinforce operational security, official comms, and...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-20</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-20.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-20.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; All vectors converge on shipping Cloud streaming with release-discipline (monorepo → plugin → cloud-v2) while restoring trust via clear migration guidance amid visible community frustration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Streaming: Launch Readiness &amp; Release Discipline:&lt;/strong&gt; Streaming is functionally working in simple flows, but the release train has critical dependencies (monorepo release, elizacloud-plugin merge, cloud-v2 core bump) plus operational blockers (NPM token ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration: Trust, Support Integrity, and Exchange Confusion:&lt;/strong&gt; The Feb 4, 2026 deadline is understood by some but still confusing in practice (“0 eligible”, exchange snapshot discrepancies), and sentiment is deteriorating. Trust-through-shipping now depends as mu...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Experience: Plugin Reliability, EVM Readiness, and Ecosystem Observability:&lt;/strong&gt; Builders are probing whether plugin-evm is truly supported while Starknet integration and provider performance changes highlight API churn and type friction. The knowledge repository and new GitHub an...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-19</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-19.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-19.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Council attention is split between execution excellence in the runtime (streaming + provider performance hardening) and a rising legitimacy risk from token migration confusion and community distrust that threatens the Cloud launch narrative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Runtime Reliability: Streaming &amp; Provider Performance Contracts:&lt;/strong&gt; Core shipped a major streaming enhancement (merged PR #6212), while an open refactor (PR #6263) proposes parallel provider execution with timeouts—signaling a push toward reliability but exposing an u...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration &amp; Exchange Coordination: Trust Incident Containment:&lt;/strong&gt; Migration confusion across exchanges (e.g., Bithumb vs Kraken handling) and user reports of a "disastrous" swap are creating a reputational gravity well; without crisp, multilingual guidance and verif...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer-First Delivery: Plugin Integration Friction &amp; Documentation Debt:&lt;/strong&gt; Builders are hitting friction integrating new plugins (Starknet type mismatches, missing handlers, unclear CLI flows) while major ecosystem PRs (Discord plugin) sit large and stale; combined with an o...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-18</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-18.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-18.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The council’s immediate leverage point is restoring trust through crisp token-migration communications and security posture while unblocking Cloud/streaming and plugin shipping decisions that prove production readiness ahead of exchange momentum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Trust, Exchange Coordination, and Safety Posture:&lt;/strong&gt; Migration remains technically possible on Solana, but exchange-specific handling (notably Bithumb vs Kraken) is producing confusion and reputational drag, compounded by community anxiety about migrati...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Streaming &amp; Messaging Plugins: Shipping Discipline Under Scale:&lt;/strong&gt; Streaming is working for simple messages/actions across cloud and monorepo, but Actions UI rendering still breaks the experience; meanwhile a massive Discord plugin PR is waiting to merge, raising qua...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Trust Through DX: Docs, Plugins, and Onboarding Clarity:&lt;/strong&gt; Builders are hitting friction in extending actions and local DB setup, while GitHub shows a surge in UX/backlog definition; the Council must convert this signal into a coherent, reliability-first onbo...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-17</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-17.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-17.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; As Kraken listing and migration chatter peak, the Council’s critical priority is preserving trust by hardening the token-migration surface area (security + exchange coordination) while simultaneously proving Cloud readiness through visible reliability wins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration &amp; Exchange-Edge Trust (Kraken/Bithumb + Site Security):&lt;/strong&gt; The migration narrative is now the public face of ElizaOS: Kraken listing (Dec 19) increases scrutiny while unresolved exchange delays and a reported migration-site compromise risk reputational damage...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Launch Readiness (Streaming UX, Auth, and Create→Publish→Monetize Loop):&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud capability is advancing (integrations, end-to-end business cycle vision), but the Council must decide what 'launch' means: a hardened minimal path with impeccable UX, or a broader platform debut...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Experience &amp; Reliability Flywheel (DB Migrations, PR Proof, AI-Assisted Workflow):&lt;/strong&gt; Developer trust is trending upward via heavy refactors, tests, and SQL/migration fixes, but field reports still show friction (Postgres permissions/migrations, foreign key failures). The Council must ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-16</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-16.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-16.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Trust is being stress-tested by token migration delays (notably Bithumb) and an alleged migration-site compromise, making incident response and clear communications the highest-leverage actions for execution excellence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Reliability &amp; Security Posture:&lt;/strong&gt; Community pressure is escalating around CEX-held migration delays and an alleged phishing/compromise of the migration site; both directly threaten the monthly directive of high-success migration and d...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Launch Trajectory (Create → Publish → Monetize → Promote):&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud progress is strong with a full business-cycle vision and new integrations/partners, but the Council must decide how to stage-access, message the value, and avoid overextending reliability during...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Framework Stability &amp; Developer Trust (DX, Testing Discipline, Data Integrity):&lt;/strong&gt; Recent GitHub momentum shows heavy refactors, dependency alignment, and Cloud-first CLI improvements, while Discord surfaces ongoing runtime friction (plugin registration errors, DB constraints) and a...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-15</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-15.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-15.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud commercialization systems (create→publish→monetize→promote) are converging toward launch, but near-term trust hinges on resolving token migration UX/documentation gaps and tightening operational safety signals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Launch Readiness &amp; Growth Loop Integrity:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud development reports strong momentum with an end-to-end business loop plus SEO/ads/social integrations, indicating a shift from tooling to ecosystem commerce. Council must decide what "launch" me...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration UX, Hardware Wallet Visibility, and Documentation Debt:&lt;/strong&gt; Token migration friction is surfacing in user reports, particularly Ledger visibility and connection pathways, creating a direct threat to the monthly directive's "high success rate" requirement. The ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reliability &amp; Safety Signals: Plugin Configuration, API Waste, and Scam Surface Area:&lt;/strong&gt; Developer friction continues via runtime errors (TEXT_LARGE tied to missing inference plugins), while operational risks include excessive Twitter-agent API calls and active scam/spam attempts in commu...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-14</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-14.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-14.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Developer trust was stressed by a “fails-on-hello” onboarding path (TEXT_LARGE + plugin install friction), signaling that Cloud/CLI defaults and documentation must eliminate inference-provider misconfiguration as we push toward launch readiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Onboarding Reliability (Inference Plugin + Updates):&lt;/strong&gt; A coder encountered TEXT_LARGE errors even on minimal prompts, traced to missing inference plugin registration; subsequent plugin installation issues were attributed to outdated packages, reinforcing ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Launch Readiness (CLI Defaults + Key Management):&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud is being positioned as the default AI provider in the CLI and a large Cloud integration PR is in flight; community questions indicate confusion about whether provider keys must be wired into Clo...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Trust &amp; Exchange Friction (Bithumb / Transparency):&lt;/strong&gt; Migration remains a reputational risk vector, with Korean users reporting blocking issues on Bithumb and community speculation about burn/sell mechanics; transparency steps exist but require clearer, ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-13</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-13.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-13.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Council attention should converge on trust restoration: a critical secrets-exfiltration vulnerability and persistent token migration friction are colliding with Cloud launch ambitions, making “secure-by-default + clear comms” the immediate path to execution excellence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Hardening: Secrets, Auth, and Production Defaults:&lt;/strong&gt; A critical vulnerability enabled unauthenticated API access to extract agent secrets due to environment variables being written into unencrypted settings; it was introduced in v1.6.4 and fixed in v1.6...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Reliability and Transparency (Bithumb + Narrative Risk):&lt;/strong&gt; Korean users report significant migration failures on Bithumb, creating prolonged frustration and price-related anxiety; unanswered questions about burns and supply handling persist. Execution excelle...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud &amp; DX Launch Readiness: CLI Integration, Stability, and Signal-to-Noise:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud integration work is accelerating (large PRs for Cloud provider defaults and CLI login/provisioning), while stability issues persist across the monorepo (TypeScript breakages, plugin-sql DB const...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-12</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-12.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-12.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Core technical foundation improvements and fixes for elizaOS are advancing while token migration issues threaten user trust and engagement with the ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Crisis Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Korean users are experiencing significant migration problems with Bithumb exchange, creating trust issues and frustration, while the continuous price decline of ELIZA raises questions about the migrat...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Foundation Strengthening:&lt;/strong&gt; The development team is making significant progress on core infrastructure with monorepo fixes, database optimizations, and standardization efforts, but performance bottlenecks and security concerns r...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Launch Strategy:&lt;/strong&gt; The ecosystem has multiple projects advancing toward launch, including Babylon as a web browser game and elizaOS Cloud integration, but clarity on timelines and feature sets remains limited....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-11</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-11.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-11.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Critical security vulnerability discovered in elizaOS server requiring immediate remediation to protect agent secrets and user data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Infrastructure Overhaul:&lt;/strong&gt; A critical security vulnerability was discovered allowing unauthorized access to agent secrets through API endpoints, requiring immediate fixes to encryption methods and authentication protocols....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cross-Chain Integration Strategy:&lt;/strong&gt; Development of Jeju testnet with cross-chain liquidity pools enables using elizaOS tokens as gas across multiple chains without bridging, opening new ecosystem expansion possibilities....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plugin System Stability:&lt;/strong&gt; Multiple users reported foreign key constraint errors with database plugins, highlighting the need for improved migration paths and stability in the plugin ecosystem....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-10</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-10.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-10.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Community concern over token migration and platform stability rising as technical teams prioritize codebase quality and next-generation features over immediate user-facing functionality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Trust &amp; Token Economics:&lt;/strong&gt; The AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration has sparked significant community frustration due to the sudden snapshot, supply increase, and declining token price, undermining confidence in the project's econo...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Delivery &amp; Timeline Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Multiple core products (ElizaOS Cloud, Babylon, Jeju) are behind communicated schedules, with the development team focused on infrastructure and technical debt rather than user-facing features, creati...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agent Architecture &amp; Capability Limitations:&lt;/strong&gt; Current agent infrastructure faces critical limitations in composability, uptime guarantees, and long-term accessibility that conflict with our mission of creating reliable 24/7 autonomous agents for ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-09</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-09.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-09.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The elizaOS.ai website security breach represents a critical vulnerability in our infrastructure that requires immediate attention to maintain trust and protect our community as we scale agent activity and prepare for v2 launch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; Current focus: Stabilize and attract new users to auto.fun by showcasing 24/7 agent activity (streaming, trading, shitposting), ship production ready elizaOS v2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Infrastructure Resilience:&lt;/strong&gt; The elizaOS.ai website was compromised with an XMR cryptocurrency miner, exposing vulnerabilities in our technical infrastructure that could impede our goal of attracting and retaining users through 2...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agent Performance Optimization:&lt;/strong&gt; Current Twitter agent limitations and discussions around streaming functionality indicate significant bottlenecks in our agent ecosystem that may prevent us from delivering the 24/7 activity required ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Confidence &amp; Tokenomics:&lt;/strong&gt; The continuous decline in token value and questions about exchange listings highlight community concerns about project sustainability, potentially undermining our ability to attract users to auto.fun ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
