<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="style.xsl"?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>elizaOS Council Briefings</title>
    <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge</link>
    <description>Strategic briefings, retrospectives, and deliberation items for elizaOS leadership</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:13:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/rss/council.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <ns0:link href="https://x.com/elizaos" rel="related" title="@elizaos on X"/>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/rss.xml" rel="related" title="GitHub Activity Feed"/>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-16</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-16.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-16.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The core team is executing a critical strategic pivot to deprioritize Eliza v2.0.0 in favor of Cloud infrastructure stabilization and token migration finalization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategic Resource Allocation: Cloud vs. v2.0:&lt;/strong&gt; Core development has been directed to halt v2.0.0 progress to ensure ElizaOS Cloud reaches the stability levels required for the beneficial AGI roadmap....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Integrity &amp; Economic Trust:&lt;/strong&gt; The ai16z-to-elizaos migration is facing technical friction and market sentiment headwinds, threatening the 'Trust Through Shipping' core principle....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-15</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-15.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-15.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The project faces a critical strategic tension between accelerating the Eliza 2.0 architectural overhaul and the current operational directive to prioritize Cloud stability to restore investor confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;V2.0 Core vs. Cloud Prioritization:&lt;/strong&gt; Core developers are navigating a major shift in priority as leadership (Borko) explicitly deprioritized v2.0 development in favor of exclusively improving Cloud infrastructure to meet the Monthly Dire...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Utility and Market Positioning:&lt;/strong&gt; The community has voiced substantial concern regarding tokenomics and utility, specifically the delay in the Jeju network which is essential for making the token functional as gas for agents....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-14</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-14.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-14.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The core development team has made a critical strategic pivot to deprioritize v2.0.0 development entirely in favor of stabilizing ElizaOS Cloud and monorepo reliability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategic Resource Realignment:&lt;/strong&gt; Core developers have shifted focus away from the Rust-based v2.0.0 rewrite to address immediate reliability and credit idempotency issues in ElizaOS Cloud....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ecosystem Identity &amp; Governance:&lt;/strong&gt; The emergence of community agents like ElizaBAO achieving affiliate status highlights a lack of formal distinction between official and third-party sector entities....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-13</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-13.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-13.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The transition toward the Jeju Network represents the critical pivot from speculative token value to utility-driven gas fee sustainability for the decentralized agent economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jeju Network &amp; Token Utility:&lt;/strong&gt; The Council must address the long-term roadmap for the Jeju Layer, which aims to convert the elizaOS token into a functional gas fee unit for autonomous agents....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaCloud App Creator Stability:&lt;/strong&gt; Developer feedback on the ElizaCloud 'App Creator' feature reveals significant friction in the non-technical user onboarding experience....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;V2.0.0 Architectural Consolidation:&lt;/strong&gt; Development activity indicates a massive structural shift toward the V2 release, focusing on Rust-based performance and core modularization....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-12</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-12.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-12.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The council must reconcile major infrastructural expansion plans (Jeju Layer) with critical user-facing friction in the current token migration and cloud deployment interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infrastructural Sovereignty vs. User Trust:&lt;/strong&gt; While leadership projects mid-2026 for the Jeju utility layer, current users are reporting critical failures in the token migration UI and basic cloud deployment....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Architectural Evolution: Eliza 2.0 and Local-First AI:&lt;/strong&gt; Proposals for a radical Eliza 2.0 runtime overhaul and local-first Claude Code alternatives suggest a shift toward hardware-agnostic sovereignty....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-11</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-11.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-11.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The transition toward Eliza 2.0 and the Jeju Layer 2 launch has introduced a critical tension between rapid technical innovation (Rust/multi-language support) and deteriorating community trust regarding token utility and transparency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Utility vs. Regulatory Optics:&lt;/strong&gt; The delisting of elizaOS/ai16z tokens from Korean exchanges due to lack of transparency in migration creates a significant barrier to the goal of 'Trust Through Shipping' and highlights the urgent nee...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eliza 2.0 Architectural Pivot:&lt;/strong&gt; The proposal for Eliza 2.0 to move toward a Rust/multi-language runtime with FFI plugin interoperability represents a massive technical leap but threatens to fragment the current developer base if not...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-10</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-10.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-10.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The focus shifted toward long-term survivability: architecting the 'Eliza 2.0' radical redesign while managing a critical regulatory delisting crisis on Korean exchanges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Architecture Evolution: Eliza 2.0 Redesign:&lt;/strong&gt; Shaw has proposed and already begun porting a radical overhaul that replaces traditional APIs and servers with a multi-language, Claude-friendly runtime. This aims to maximize framework reliability an...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Utility and Regional Regulatory Pressure:&lt;/strong&gt; The coordinated delisting from Korean exchanges (Bithumb, Korbit, Coinone) due to 'transparency concerns' highlights a critical need for clearly defined token utility and public communication strategi...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-09</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-09.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-09.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The council faces a critical split between managing a 'delisting crisis' on Korean exchanges due to transparency issues and a radical architectural pivot toward Eliza 2.0 with multi-language FFI interoperability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regulatory Integrity &amp; Exchange Relations:&lt;/strong&gt; Coordinated delistings by DAXA (Bithumb, Coinone, Korbit) cite a lack of transparency in the token migration process and failure to disclose material information....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Architectural Evolution: Eliza 2.0:&lt;/strong&gt; A proposal for a multi-language runtime (TS, Rust, Python) aims to turn plugins into interoperable 'skills' while removing server/API overhead for a more 'Claude-friendly' runtime....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Trillion-Dollar Data Graph:&lt;/strong&gt; The transition from execution-only agents to high-quality data collection (Babylon, Jeju, and Mocap suits) to build context graphs....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-08</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-08.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-08.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Navigating critical version 1.7.0 stability issues and external exchange delistings while laying foundations for the Jeju Layer 2 and Bazaar ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Execution Excellence vs. Release Velocity:&lt;/strong&gt; Recent breaking changes in core serverId handling (v1.7.0) have caused ecosystem-wide downtime for Discord users, threatening the core principle of reliability....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Presence and Regulatory Resilience:&lt;/strong&gt; The delisting of AI16Z/ElizaOS from major Korean exchanges (DAXA) due to 'transparency concerns' creates a significant narrative and liquidity hurdle....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The 'Bazaar' and Jeju Scaling Strategy:&lt;/strong&gt; Development is shifting toward the Jeju Layer 2 and a decentralized agent marketplace (Bazaar), requiring a new architectural standard for connector gateways....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-07</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-07.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-07.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The Council prioritizes stabilizing the 1.7.0 core architecture by addressing critical breaking changes in Discord integration and database migrations while balancing the rapid influx of high-level performance optimizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stability vs. Innovation Velocity:&lt;/strong&gt; The transition to v1.7.0 has introduced critical breaking changes in server identification and database migration patterns, threatening the 'Execution Excellence' core principle. While performance PRs...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Technical Edge: The 'Earning Agent' Paradigm:&lt;/strong&gt; Community interest is shifting toward autonomous agents capable of on-chain execution with guardrails (Prediction markets, DeFi utilities via Spartan). This presents a strategic opportunity to move be...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-06</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-06.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-06.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Transitioning the framework architecture toward modular 'skills' while addressing critical memory consumption bottlenecks in the build pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Modular Architecture: Plugins to Skills:&lt;/strong&gt; To improve composability and DX, the team is proposing a strategic pivot to convert all existing plugins into modular 'skills'....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operational Infrastructure Scarcity:&lt;/strong&gt; Critical performance bottlenecks, specifically excessive memory usage (21GB+) during builds, are threatening local development efficiency....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-05</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-05.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-05.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Today's focus shifted from raw feature expansion to critical infrastructure stabilization, specifically targeting a memory consumption crisis in the build pipeline and major SQL performance bottlenecks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operational Reliability &amp; Build Stability:&lt;/strong&gt; Serious intermittent memory spikes (21GB-27GB+) in the Turbo build process threaten CI/CD reliability and developer onboarding. Engineering must address whether this is a structural framework leak or ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategic Ecosystem Philosophy:&lt;/strong&gt; Internal debate on tokenomics pairing suggests a crossroads between an open-source 'freedom' model and an integrated 'routing' model similar to competitors like Virtuals. The core vision remains a dec...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Infrastructure Hardening:&lt;/strong&gt; Major technical debt was cleared today via SQL fixes and unified transport hooks, but critical dependency bugs (Anthropic/OpenAI MCP fallback) reveal fragility in multi-model interoperability....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-04</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-04.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-04.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The focus shifted toward identifying UI/UX friction and stabilizing core infrastructure to support the transition to the ElizaOS Cloud launch and public agent ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operational Reliability &amp; Resource Optimization:&lt;/strong&gt; Critical performance bottlenecks, including extreme memory consumption during builds and SQL parameterization errors, threaten the 'Execution Excellence' mandate....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next-Gen Autonomy &amp; Agency Boundaries:&lt;/strong&gt; Emergent frameworks like roseOS and concepts for AI-powered infrastructure migration suggest a shift toward high-stakes autonomous decision-making....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-03</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-03.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-03.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The transition from v1.6 stability to v2 architecture is accelerating via aggressive core refactoring, the emergence of agency-boundary frameworks like roseOS, and ambitious 'Jeju' cloud infrastructure prototypes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operational Reliability &amp; Technical Maturity:&lt;/strong&gt; Critical architectural patches for streaming and SQL stability are being prioritized alongside a new linter to ensure cross-ecosystem logging standards....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategic Infrastructure &amp; Jeju Expansion:&lt;/strong&gt; Proposals for 'Eliza DWS Transform' suggest a pivot toward autonomous cloud migration agents that challenge legacy providers like AWS....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Economics &amp; Migration Integrity:&lt;/strong&gt; Technical friction in Tangem wallet migration represents a risk to community trust during the month's primary directive....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-02</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-02.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-02.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Transitioning from tactical bug-squashing to strategic ecosystem architectural planning for public agent deployment and decentralized infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Agent Discovery &amp; UX Monetization:&lt;/strong&gt; Development suggests a shift toward a governed public agent marketplace with structured discovery, forking capabilities, and optimized credit systems to drive user retention....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Decentralized Infrastructure &amp; Infrastructure Migration:&lt;/strong&gt; Exploration of migrating from AWS to the Jeju network via autonomous 'migration agents' signals a core move toward sovereign hardware....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gaming &amp; Metaverse Integration ('Hyperscape'):&lt;/strong&gt; Strategic pivot toward embedding Eliza agents within existing gaming environments (RuneScape/Zelda style) rather than isolated chat interfaces....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2026-01-01</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-01.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2026-01-01.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The Council must pivot from internal framework stabilization to the deployment of resilient cloud-native infrastructure on 'Jeju' to transition the ecosystem toward a public-facing decentralized AI economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jeju Infrastructure &amp; Decentralization Timeline:&lt;/strong&gt; The migration of service infrastructure to the Jeju platform is a prerequisite for the public launch of Cloud and Babylon products, signaling a shift from centralized hosting (AWS) to self-owned physi...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration &amp; Economic Trust:&lt;/strong&gt; As the migration from AI16Z to ElizaOS concludes in February, the Council must ensure token utility and documentation meet the needs of a wider investor base to sustain current positive sentiment....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Autonomous Trade &amp; DegenAI Integration:&lt;/strong&gt; The development of DegenAI as a flagship autonomous trading agent creates a high-stakes test case for the framework's reliability and its ability to handle cross-chain financial operations....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-31</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-31.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-31.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; End-of-month execution hinges on converting renewed token momentum into trust: de-risk the migration and clarify token/ecosystem messaging while shipping reliability upgrades (hooks, logging, plugins) that make Cloud onboarding frictionless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Integrity &amp; Public Trust:&lt;/strong&gt; Community sentiment surged with a major price move tied to Shaw’s return to X, but operational risk remains: migration confusion, wallet-edge cases, and role verification gaps are eroding trust and co...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud + Jeju Infrastructure Trajectory:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud beta is live with light support and Jeju is framed as a compute marketplace launching on AWS first, then migrating toward permissionless physical infrastructure—an ambitious path that requires c...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Framework Reliability &amp; Developer Experience (Hooks, Streaming, Plugins):&lt;/strong&gt; Core work is trending toward execution excellence: unified hooks across transports, database logging for streaming LLM calls, and plugin fixes (OpenAI image gen + caching). However, release/versioning...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annual Summary: Year 2025</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-annual-summary.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-annual-summary.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Executive Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Across 2025, ElizaOS substantially expanded capability and modernized its foundations: the plugin ecosystem and AI provider surface grew rapidly, social/real-time clients widened the public-facing footprint, and core architecture moved toward modular, agent-scoped, multi-tenant readiness. The product also matured with a redesigned management UI, better observability, and multiple refactors (eventing, messaging, server separation) that collectively set a stronger baseline for cloud deployment and...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Achievements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capability expansion (plugins, chains/DeFi, providers, models, voice):&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core architecture modernization (modularity, eventing, runtime, messaging, server separation):&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product surface improvements (UI, observability, management workflows):&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knowledge/memory and multi-agent foundations:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social and real-time presence expansion:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>annual</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-30</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-30.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-30.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; The fleet is riding a surge of public attention while simultaneously absorbing migration friction and cloud-beta edge cases—making trust-through-reliability the decisive battlefield for the next 72 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Integrity &amp; Support Load:&lt;/strong&gt; Migration is functionally live (snapshot taken; multi-chain availability confirmed), but repeated user errors and eligibility confusion are creating support drag and reputational risk at the exact mom...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Beta &amp; Jeju Compute-Marketplace Trajectory:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud is in open beta with “light support,” while Jeju is positioned as a decentralized Vercel alternative (compute marketplace, distributed cache, DNS, serverless SQLite). The strategic risk is promi...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Trust: DX, Data Layer Choices, and Quality Gates:&lt;/strong&gt; Docs and tooling progress is strong (multiple PRs merged; hot reload; docs improvements), but recurring “death by papercut” bugs (agent naming crashes, share-link errors, Windows setup friction) and s...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-29</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-29.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-29.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; A major Jeju+Babylon cloud marketplace breakthrough is now in tension with execution excellence: reliability, SLAs, and clear public definitions (migration eligibility + official affiliations) must be hardened immediately to protect developer trust and the Cloud launch narrative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jeju+Babylon Cloud Marketplace: From Breakthrough to Trustworthy Platform:&lt;/strong&gt; Shaw reports Cloud services running on both Jeju and Babylon, positioning ElizaOS as a decentralized Vercel alternative with DNS, cache, and SQLite compatibility plus claimed cost reductions. The Coun...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Friction: Snapshot Policy, UX Failures, and Trust Recovery:&lt;/strong&gt; Users continue reporting migration blockers (wallet connection issues, ineligible snapshot confusion, and &quot;max amount reached&quot; errors), while policy states no post-snapshot purchases are eligible. Thi...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Trust Surface Area: Naming Bugs, Login/Deploy Errors, and Shipping Cadence:&lt;/strong&gt; Reliability gaps are surfacing in core UX (agent naming edge cases like &quot;null&quot; or numeric causing exceptions) alongside Cloud login/deploy issues and streaming/UI roughness. Meanwhile, the latest dail...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Council Briefing: 2025-12-28</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-28.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/council_briefing/2025-12-28.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Focus:&lt;/strong&gt; Operational momentum bifurcated: public trust friction intensified around snapshot-based token migration while core engineering surfaced a bold Jeju/Eliza Cloud future—yet daily GitHub throughput dipped to near-idle, risking execution credibility at month-end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monthly Goal:&lt;/em&gt; December 2025: Execution excellence—complete token migration with high success rate, launch ElizaOS Cloud, stabilize flagship agents, and build developer trust through reliability and clear documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Topics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration Clarity &amp; Trust Repair:&lt;/strong&gt; Snapshot-locked migration policy is generating repeated user failure modes (&quot;max amount reached&quot; / &quot;0 eligible&quot;) and compounding reputational damage during a major price drawdown. The Council must dec...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ElizaOS Cloud Reliability &amp; Developer Experience Gaps:&lt;/strong&gt; Cloud is live and attracting projects, but edge-case failures (agent naming, deployment credentials, UI multistep streaming) are breaking the “seamless UX” promise. The Council should prioritize a sma...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jeju Distributed Cloud Trajectory vs. Month-End Execution Risk:&lt;/strong&gt; Jeju’s vision (TEE-secured, proof-of-cloud, sharded KMS, serverless SQLite) is strategically aligned with cross-chain, unstoppable agents—but the immediate signal shows low day-to-day repo activity an...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarterly Summary: Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-Q4-summary.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-Q4-summary.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Executive Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Q4 2025 was a “foundation-first” quarter: ElizaOS made significant progress on core architecture, reliability, security, and monorepo health—laying groundwork for scale (Cloud, marketplace, multi-tenant deployments) and for higher-quality real-time agent UX via streaming. The engineering trajectory strengthened (server refactor, unified messaging APIs, entity-level security, TypeScript/build stabilization), and the plugin ecosystem continued to mature with practical integrations.

In parallel, t...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Achievements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core architecture &amp; reliability (scale readiness):&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security posture improvements (with remaining gaps):&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer experience &amp; delivery health:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ecosystem &amp; monetization foundations:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-time agent UX (streaming) initiated:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>quarterly</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Retro: December 2025</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-12-retro.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-12-retro.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Premise:&lt;/strong&gt; The JedAI Council reviews December 2025: a month of deep core hardening (refactors, type safety, dependency upgrades, security fixes), early groundwork for real-time streaming across model providers, and a parallel wave of UX planning—while community trust was stressed by token migration friction, support gaps, and multi-user architecture uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;December delivered meaningful foundational progress: the core server was refactored for reliability and cleanliness, monorepo build health improved, and at least one critical security issue (secret handling/auth) was addressed. The plugin ecosystem expanded (DeFi, OpenChat, Farcaster local hub), and...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Developments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core server reliability &amp; architecture:&lt;/strong&gt; Major server refactor and optimization in elizaos/eliza improved structure, reliability patterns, and performance; additional work opened to address c...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monorepo health &amp; type safety:&lt;/strong&gt; Resolved TypeScript build errors across the monorepo and updated dependencies, reducing breakage and improving maintainability....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security hardening:&lt;/strong&gt; Fixed critical vulnerabilities related to character secret encryption and server authentication exposure (ELIZA_SERVER_AUTH_TOKEN), though the ecosyst...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Streaming groundwork (real-time agents):&lt;/strong&gt; Initiated streaming support across OpenAI, Anthropic, and OpenRouter plugins—setting up real-time conversational experiences as a platform primitive....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plugin ecosystem expansion:&lt;/strong&gt; Registry added new community plugins (Moralis DeFi, OpenChat, self-hosted Farcaster hub), extending Web3 and comms capabilities and reducing third-par...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>monthly</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Retro: November 2025</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-11-retro.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-11-retro.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Premise:&lt;/strong&gt; The JedAI Council convenes for their November retrospective to assess the critical month of token migration, technical advances, and community challenges. As the AI16Z to ElizaOS migration unfolds and key infrastructure pieces fall into place, the council must chart the path forward for December.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;November proved to be a pivotal transition month with the AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration taking center stage alongside significant technical developments. While infrastructure improvements like entity-level security and agent persistence fixes showed strong progress toward v2, community concerns a...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Developments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration:&lt;/strong&gt; AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration launched with 1:6 ratio but faced user experience challenges including portal issues, CEX support gaps, and documenta...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core Infrastructure:&lt;/strong&gt; Critical bug fixes for agent settings persistence and new entity-level security implementation significantly improved system reliability...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platform Expansion:&lt;/strong&gt; New development streams including x402 payment middleware, voice infrastructure, and cross-platform integrations show progress toward v2...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agent Products:&lt;/strong&gt; Otaku agent entered beta with reported issues around price data accuracy and LP staking functionality...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Relations:&lt;/strong&gt; Ongoing X lawsuit demands and migration confusion created community friction despite technical progress...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>monthly</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Retro: October 2025</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-10-retro.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-10-retro.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Premise:&lt;/strong&gt; The JedAI Council convenes for their monthly retrospective as October 2025 closes out with significant architectural milestones but persistent community friction around the token migration. The framework is maturing rapidly while the ecosystem faces growing pains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;October marked a pivotal month where ElizaOS achieved major technical milestones in framework modularity and developer experience while simultaneously grappling with token migration uncertainties and community communication challenges. The council debates whether to prioritize technical excellence o...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Developments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core Architecture:&lt;/strong&gt; Major plugin/config module overhaul with UUID-based agent identification and unified messaging APIs...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Experience:&lt;/strong&gt; CLI refactoring and critical import bug fixes, but persistent onboarding friction for new developers...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Migration:&lt;/strong&gt; AI16Z to ElizaOS migration delayed with community confusion and limited exchange support clarity...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategic Partnerships:&lt;/strong&gt; IoTeX Real-World AI Foundry partnership and Claude Agent SDK integration expanding ecosystem reach...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Security concerns with fake accounts and moderation challenges during migration period...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>monthly</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarterly Summary: Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-Q3-summary.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-Q3-summary.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Executive Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Q3 2025 marked a critical maturation phase for ElizaOS, characterized by significant architectural achievements alongside emerging stability challenges. The quarter began with major developer experience improvements and UI redesigns, establishing a strong foundation for v2. However, external dependencies proved fragile with the X/Twitter account suspension, while internal technical debt accumulated, culminating in a CLI crisis that threatened core user workflows. The period revealed a fundamenta...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Achievements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Experience Revolution:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UI/UX Modernization:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core Architecture Evolution:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Infrastructure Breakthrough:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>quarterly</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Retro: September 2025</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-09-retro.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-09-retro.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Premise:&lt;/strong&gt; The JedAI Council convenes for their monthly retrospective to assess September's developments, focusing on the major CLI architecture crisis, growing technical debt concerns, and community confidence challenges that emerged despite steady technical progress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;September revealed a critical tension between ambitious feature development and architectural stability. While the team made significant progress on core functionality and developer tooling, the CLI crisis and mounting technical debt exposed the need for a more disciplined approach to infrastructure...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Developments:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLI Architecture Crisis:&lt;/strong&gt; Major CLI instability requiring emergency reversion and architectural redesign discussions...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Debt Accumulation:&lt;/strong&gt; TypeScript compilation errors, build warnings, and platform compatibility issues mounting...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Confidence Erosion:&lt;/strong&gt; Token concerns, documentation gaps, and communication issues affecting user trust...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core Feature Progress:&lt;/strong&gt; Dynamic prompting, image generation fixes, and enhanced testing capabilities delivered...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Experience Improvements:&lt;/strong&gt; Unified NPM workflows, Docker support, and build system standardization...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>monthly</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarterly Summary: Q2 2025</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-Q2-summary.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-Q2-summary.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Executive Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Q2 2025 marked a pivotal quarter for ElizaOS, culminating in the successful launch of v2.0 with major architectural improvements including server separation, agent-scoped plugins, and unified testing frameworks. The development velocity remained strong with consistent high-impact releases across CLI modernization, AI provider ecosystem expansion, and enhanced developer tooling. However, this technical progress was overshadowed by persistent reliability issues, particularly with Twitter integrati...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Achievements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platform Maturation:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Provider Ecosystem:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Experience:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Engagement:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>quarterly</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarterly Summary: Q1 2025</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-Q1-summary.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/retros/2025-Q1-summary.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Executive Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Q1 2025 was defined by outsized capability expansion and major architectural shifts, alongside growing pressure on reliability, onboarding, and trust surfaces. ElizaOS meaningfully widened its ecosystem reach (chains/DeFi/data providers), increased AI-provider portability, and expanded real-time/social agent presence (Twitter Spaces, Instagram, XMTP), while simultaneously investing in foundational changes (dynamic plugin loading, DB multi-tenancy primitives, and a redesigned agent management UI)...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Achievements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ecosystem &amp; capability expansion (Web3, data, infra):&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model/provider portability (reduced lock-in):&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-time + social presence expansion:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platform architecture modernization (modularity + runtime):&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-agent foundation &amp; data model hardening:&lt;/strong&gt; ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>quarterly</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
