<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="style.xsl"?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>elizaOS Daily Intelligence</title>
    <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge</link>
    <description>Daily facts and insights from the elizaOS ecosystem</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:10:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/rss/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <ns0:link href="https://x.com/elizaos" rel="related" title="@elizaos on X"/>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/rss.xml" rel="related" title="GitHub Activity Feed"/>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-13</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-13.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-13.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Error: Failed to generate briefing due to LLM or parsing issues.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://cdn.elizaos.news/elizaos-media/embed-image-1460360263785119834_ab47938d.jpg" type="image/png" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-12</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-12.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-12.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Error: Failed to generate briefing due to LLM or parsing issues.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-11</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-11.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-11.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Error: Failed to generate briefing due to LLM or parsing issues.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-09</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-10.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-10.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Core developers discussed a major Eliza 2.0 runtime redesign (removing API/server/CLI/projects) alongside a parallel initiative to convert plugins into interoperable “skills.” In the broader community, token migration and exchange delisting concerns persisted while cloud/app-creator stability, plugin fixes, and new database/auth improvements progressed on GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;V2.0.0 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: plugin-bootstrap (+ sql minor) actions/providers for serverId =&gt; messageServerId change (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: Enable hot reload for backend development (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: unified hooks with multi-transport support (HTTP/SSE/WebSocket) (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A critical P1 issue was opened to investigate a publishing failure preventing the Discord plugin release v1.3.4 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion was mostly non-technical, with notable items including a proposal to integrate Behavidence’s Dopa One (dopamine/mental-health monitoring via phone/wearable interactions) into a future Eliza...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developers discussed ElizaCloud app-creator failures (reported by one user, confirmed working as an early feature by cjft), cloud billing page updates, an unanswered question about Twitter API require...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core-dev discussion centered on two initiatives: (1) converting plugins into interoperable skills (folders with .md instructions + deterministic scripts) including a hooks-based approach for implicit ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-08</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-09.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-09.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion centered on the confirmed February/March 2026 Korean exchange delistings tied to the AI16Z→ElizaOS rebrand/swap transparency, alongside ongoing token migration eligibility/LP errors and unanswered questions about token utility. In parallel, engineering activity focused on resolving ElizaOS v1.7.0 Discord/serverId compatibility issues and improving core/client transports and plugin-sql security/serverless support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(plugin-sql): add Neon serverless support &amp; improve RLS security (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: plugin-bootstrap (+ sql minor) actions/providers for serverId =&gt; messageServerId change (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: unified hooks with multi-transport support (HTTP/SSE/WebSocket) (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P1 publishing failure preventing plugin-discord v1.3.4 release (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Telegram plugin crashes when processing certain images (TypeError on photos) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users discussed AI16Z→ElizaOS migration failures (including LP &quot;max amount reached&quot;), conflicting guidance about whether exchanges auto-migrate balances, and the confirmed Korean exchange delistings t...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical discussion covered Eliza’s data foundation and context graphs, Jeju/Bazaar positioning, and deployment options (PGlite vs PostgreSQL). Multiple data-collection proposals were shared (phone a...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core-devs discussed integrating high-quality daily/weekly/monthly agentic workflow insights into last-mile applications (agents, webhooks, apps) and noted that inference markets have not been highly p...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-07</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-08.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-08.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS v1.7.0 Discord bot integrations were failing with &quot;No server ID found&quot; errors due to incomplete `serverId` → `messageServerId` migration, prompting an urgent fix path (PR #6333 / odi-17 branch) and guidance to temporarily downgrade to v1.6.5. In parallel, core-dev discussions advanced connector scaling architecture (event pumps), cloud reliability work (TOCTOU mitigation), and documentation/community issues (model naming format, contract address discoverability).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: plugin-bootstrap (+ sql minor) actions/providers for serverId =&gt; messageServerId change (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PR #6339: skip pgcrypto extension when using PGLite (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chat Box UI Improvement - Dynamic Sizing (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiated work to transition from sendMessage to handleMessage (unified API alignment) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publishing failure preventing release of version v1.3.4 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users reported Discord bot failures on ElizaOS v1.7.0 with &quot;No server ID found&quot; errors; Odilitime identified an incomplete `serverId` → `messageServerId` migration and provided a fix branch (odi-17) p...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; A developer integrating elizaoscloud agents reported &quot;Model not found&quot; errors; cjft provided the required provider-prefixed `model` format (e.g., openai/..., anthropic/..., google/...), and ElizaBAO c...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core-devs discussed urgent fixes for v1.7.0 (PR #6333) and the need to test Discord compatibility across branches before cutting a new Discord release. Architecture discussion focused on connector sca...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://cdn.elizaos.news/elizaos-media/screenshot_2026-01-06_at_4-28-45_pm_74425714.png" type="image/png" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-05</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-07.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-07.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discord discussion centered on API integration quirks (Anthropic + embeddings), token/ecosystem monetization ideas, and near-term feature concepts, while GitHub activity shows continued maintenance work focused on messaging transports, SQL plugin reliability, and plugin security upgrades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: unified hooks with multi-transport support (HTTP/SSE/WebSocket) (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): use sql.raw() for SET LOCAL to avoid parameterization errors (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): add pool config, error handler, and fix PGLite shutdown (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(default-message-service): optimize provider handling in MultiStep (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change free credits from $5 to $1 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;multiple-channels:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion included token/ecosystem monetization ideas (e.g., token pairing), confusion about unrelated &quot;Eliza token&quot; branding, and feature concepts like an AI arena/colosseum with betting. Technical ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;multiple-channels:&lt;/em&gt; Updates included continued development on DegenAI, progress on Eliza knowledge data pipelines with upcoming documentation/presentation, and polymarket phase 2 repo updates. Technical discussion detail...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-04</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-06.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-06.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community discussions focused on agent architecture (multi-model setups, RoseOS framework) and operational bottlenecks (Turbo build memory usage, plugin versioning). In parallel, GitHub activity emphasized platform reliability/UX fixes and ongoing plugin security/performance work (notably Twitter OAuth2 PKCE and improved OpenAI media handling).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): use sql.raw() for SET LOCAL to avoid parameterization… (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(default-message-service): optimize provider handling in MultiStep (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work started on OAuth2 PKCE authentication flow (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix image descriptions and add caching for audio/image handlers (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add community plugin `plugin-coinrailz` to registry (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;overall:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion included RoseOS (a framework on ElizaOS), multi-model agent setups using Openrouter/provider configuration, guidance to deploy agents with custom plugins via cloud containers using the Eliz...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;overall:&lt;/em&gt; Updates included continued DegenAI development, progress on Eliza knowledge data pipelines with upcoming documentation/presentation, and Polymarket Phase 2 repository updates. Technical trading discus...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-05</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-05.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-05.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion and development activity centered on improving agent reliability and operability (logging standards, faster multi-provider execution, and data-isolation DB correctness) while expanding deployment/model-provider flexibility (OpenRouter multi-model setups, cloud container deployments). Product work and requests emphasized public-agent UX states, message limits for anonymous users, and higher-quality chat summaries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): use sql.raw() for SET LOCAL to avoid parameterizatio… (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(default-message-service): optimize provider handling in MultiStep (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore(license): update year to 2026 (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chat summaries don't really make much sense. Can we improve (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Limit messages for non-signed up user to ~2-3 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#general:&lt;/em&gt; Key discussion topics included multi-model agent setups using OpenRouter configuration, deploying agents (including custom plugins) via cloud containers, and recent logging improvements attributed to ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-03</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-04.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-04.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion and development updates centered on ElizaOS as a composable agent framework, with active guidance on multi-model agent setups and cloud container deployments. On the engineering side, provider execution was optimized, logging standards were reinforced with a linter, and GitHub activity included a SQL plugin fix plus new UX issues filed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(default-message-service): optimize provider handling in MultiStep (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): use sql.raw() for SET LOCAL to avoid parameterization issues (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scroll should work on whole page (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connect wallet should ideally go straight to wallet options (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation included high-level positioning of ElizaOS as an open-source framework for autonomous agents ('Linux' analogy) and an introduction of roseOS as an experimental framework built on ElizaOS ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical guidance focused on configuring multi-model agents (e.g., Anthropic and OpenAI together) using the Openrouter plugin with env-defined providers, and deploying agents with custom plugins via ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core dev discussion noted improved logging work tied to PR #6263 and a new log-format linter in eliza/config intended to be integrated across projects and plugins; a separate thread shared an 'agentic...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-02</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-03.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-03.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Activity centered on UX and access-control changes for public agents (message limits, public agent UI states, improved summaries) alongside continued community friction around AI16z→ElizaOS token migration and wallet compatibility. Core-dev discussion referenced ongoing PR review work (streaming-related) and plugin development (plugin-github updates and a new plugin-git).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change free credits from $5 to $1 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public agent cards should have chat number (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Separate public agent states (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Limit messages for non-signed up user to ~2-3 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chat summaries don't really make much sense. Can we improve (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation included token migration questions and wallet issues (reports of tokens not showing after transfers to Phantom), plus a brief redirection of an NFT smart contract question to the coders c...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Community discussed contributing and plugins; an unanswered question asked whether an entire GitHub codebase could be imported as an agent, and Odilitime shared the plugin-github repo while noting ong...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; DorianD proposed an AI 'cost reduction and migration agent' to analyze AWS usage and migrate workloads to cheaper alternatives, referencing the VersusControl/ai-infrastructure-agent project....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-01</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-02.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-02.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion centered on agentic game development (a RuneScape fork aiming for a “Zelda with agents” experience) and required features for Hyperscape tooling, alongside recurring community questions about token migration, token contract details, and token utility/integration with cloud services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critical fix to ensure streaming LLM calls are properly logged to the database (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modernize CLI toolchain to use Bun-native processes (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Standardize internal server communication routes (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add core support for Chain-of-Thought (CoT) reasoning (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refactor the internal messaging system / messaging API redesign (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation was dominated by New Year greetings plus repeated questions about token contract details and migration from AI16Z to ElizaOS; a roadmap question was answered with the GitHub roadmap link,...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; A new member joined referencing Shaw; Kenk asked whether Eliza can be used to manage and schedule Farcaster posts, with no answer captured in the provided segment....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core-dev discussion focused on an agentic game concept: forking a RuneScape project into a Zelda-like experience where Eliza agents (and Spartan) populate towns and generate quests; Shaw listed missin...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-31</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-01.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-01.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Work centered on Jeju Network backend progress (including an OAuth3 testnet nameserver routed via on-chain registry to IPFS), continued preparation for Cloud/Babylon launches, and ongoing ElizaOS token migration logistics. Community discussions also covered DegenAI’s 1M-token autotrader gating, documentation gaps around token info, and wallet/migration support issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure streaming LLM calls are properly logged to the database (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Standardize internal server message routes (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix image descriptions and introduce caching for audio and image handlers (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement OAuth2 PKCE authentication flow (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add community-created plugin-coinrailz to the registry (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion included migration and chain availability questions (BSC and Solana), DegenAI’s 1M-token autotrader gating and referenced stack partners (Chainlink, Cambrian), and user reports of Phantom d...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Jin described an image pipeline that generates art from summarized Discord/GitHub activity with date-based seasonal variance and a goal of newspaper-style visuals; an additional report mentioned an un...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Shaw mentioned migrating infrastructure to run on Jeju in preparation for going public after launching Cloud and Babylon; discussion also included speculative market commentary (capital rotation; debt...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-30</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-31.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-31.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community activity centered on a reported ~120% $elizaOS price move following Shaw regaining access to X and discussing Jeju infrastructure plans. In parallel, engineering work progressed on unified hooks (multi-transport) and streaming LLM logging fixes, while users continued to seek clarity and support for the AI16Z→ElizaOS migration and token information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unified hooks with multi-transport support (HTTP/SSE/WebSocket) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(core): log streaming LLM calls to database (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;saftey → safety (typo fix) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My agent cards resizing to match dashboard agent cards (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unslop Apps (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users discussed the reported ~$elizaOS price move tied to Shaw returning to X, asked migration questions about AI16Z→ElizaOS, and requested clearer token information and role verification processes (e...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Builders shared agent-development resources (skills repo and OpenSouls integration), discussed Twitter API cost constraints ($200/month), and exchanged implementation details for embedding ElizaCloud ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Shaw described Jeju’s infrastructure plan (AWS first, then self-owned racks). Kenk noted tokenomics documentation updates and short-term plans to add CoinGecko links; documentation requests included a...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-29</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-30.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-30.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS community attention centered on the project and Shaw returning to X (Twitter) and an associated large Twitter Space, while product work continued with Eliza Cloud open beta, cross-chain token availability, and multiple merged GitHub improvements. Ongoing friction remained around the AI16Z→ElizaOS migration process and a set of developer-facing setup/UX bugs reported in Discord.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(server): standardize message server route naming (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs(plugin-dummy-services): add comprehensive README (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(cli): replace execa and child_process with Bun.spawn and bun-exec utilities (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs: fix documentation inconsistencies and add missing test flags (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When clicking on agent, if it has at least one conversation, open that conversation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Community discussion included confirmation of new agents released to production, cross-chain token availability, migration snapshot completion, Eliza Cloud beta availability, contract-address sharing,...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developer support questions focused on Windows setup issues for a DaVinci Resolve MCP integration (Python import error) and an unresolved error when chatting with an agent via share link....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core development discussion included review needs for PR #6285, a docs PR (#81) for Cloud integration and monorepo coverage, a proposed Branded UUIDs PR, Discord plugin PR #36 logging improvements (ch...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-28</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-29.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-29.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Core developers discussed a decentralized cloud marketplace running on Jeju and Babylon, framed as an on-chain alternative to Vercel with integrated DNS, caching, and database components. In parallel, migration usability issues and ecosystem/affiliation confusion continued to generate user support load.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snapshot Eligibility Issue + Tangem Wallet Connection Not Supported (Discord Support Compromised) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users asked for clarification about which projects are officially affiliated with elizaOS (e.g., Zora) and reported migration issues including wallet connection and token exchange problems; multiple u...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; A brief exchange referenced a trading bot and mentioned complexity-science informed Bayesian inference, without sharing implementation details....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Shaw announced cloud services running on Jeju and Babylon and described a decentralized Vercel-like compute marketplace including agents/inference, DNS/domain purchasing, distributed cache, and a SQLi...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-27</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-28.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-28.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion centered on AI16Z→ElizaOS migration constraints and unresolved tokenomics questions, alongside engineering updates including the proposed “jeju” distributed cloud platform and multiple ElizaCloud usability/validation bugs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snapshot Eligibility Issue + Tangem Wallet Connection Not Supported (Discord Support Compromised) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Add ElizaOS Cloud as Default AI Provider in CLI (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: enhance streaming support in text generation (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users requested Eliza Cloud API endpoint information (answered as available on the site), asked about migration limits, and discussed identifying projects as built on “elizaos cloud” for distribution....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Bug reports included agent-name validation failures (“null” and numeric names causing exceptions) and a deployment failure involving ECR credentials/repository discovery when using `elizaos deploy`. U...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Migration policy was reiterated: only snapshot-held tokens can be migrated and post-snapshot purchases are excluded. DorianD asked whether ElizaOS will be Jeju’s native token; Borko responded that tok...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-26</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-27.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-27.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS Cloud officially launched and immediately saw community agent-building activity, alongside active engineering work on streaming, workflows, and authentication improvements. In parallel, Discord discussions centered on token price drawdown and lingering friction from the AI16Z→ElizaOS migration, including exchange-related concerns and requests for clearer token utility documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhance multi-step workflow with retry logic and parameter extraction capabilities (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Standardize naming conventions for message server routes (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion focused on the project’s transition from AI16Z meme coin roots to utility, token drawdown (90–98% from ATH), migration friction (snapshot-based eligibility and exchange confusion), and the ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developers discussed Cloud/agent technical issues (deployment username-null error, file uploads, Ollama model configuration) and tooling constraints (bun required; npm not supported). A workaround for...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Jeju Network questions centered on decentralization goals (confirmed as core) and an unanswered question on whether Jeju’s token will be $elizaos; a previously mentioned “life-changing event” expected...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-25</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-26.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-26.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion centered on the AI16Z→ElizaOS token migration, ongoing price decline, and exchange-support risk, while the team continued positioning Eliza Cloud as the primary near-term tokenomics/value-accrual mechanism. Development and roadmap work continued in parallel, including Cloud beta onboarding and upcoming mainnet milestones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snapshot Eligibility Issue + Tangem Wallet Connection Not Supported (Discord Support Compromised) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation focused on migration eligibility (Nov 11 snapshot wallet requirement), token mintability for Chainlink CCIP, migration rationale (moving off token2022 for exchange compatibility), token u...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Participants compared ElizaOS FDV (~$22M) to competitors (Pippin, Virtuals), discussed communication expectations, and reiterated that Cloud rollout is tied to implementing tokenomics....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Shaw proposed splitting Babylon into points and non-points components, with the points game using Eliza Cloud for inference/authentication and a stated target of migrating 350,000 users; discussion al...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-24</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-25.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-25.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion centered on ElizaOS token value accrual and how Eliza Cloud revenue will be used, alongside near-term Cloud feature clarifications (upload limits, planned custom model hosting). Development updates emphasized documentation cleanup, plugin work (including Starknet), and CI reliability issues tied to Claude billing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monorepo documentation needs fixing (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problems with spacing in numbered items (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conversation duplication bug (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opening agent chat should show most recent conversation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation focused on tokenomics and value accrual; team clarified that Eliza Cloud revenue (not yield) will be used for token buybacks, with further token utility planned for the Jeju release. Migr...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developer-focused discussion included plugin-starknet updates and guidance on building knowledge-backed agents in ElizaOS Cloud, including a 50MB upload limit, Markdown preference, and planned custom ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Debate on tokenomics compared ElizaOS to Virtual’s pairing model; team response emphasized token value tied to product usage and infrastructure development. Unusual sell patterns were discussed with s...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
