<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>elizaOS Daily Intelligence</title>
    <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge</link>
    <description>Daily facts and insights from the elizaOS ecosystem</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 02:20:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/rss/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-16</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-17.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-17.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community focus centered on token migration logistics and credibility signals (Kraken listing on Dec 19; migration delays and a reported migration-site compromise), alongside steady engineering progress on cloud enablement, authentication, and developer workflow automation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Unified API - serverless - nodejs (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): migrate to messageService API and auto-create PGLite directories (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Add ElizaOS Cloud as Default AI Provider in CLI (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Primary discussion centered on AI16Z→ElizaOS migration mechanics and a key credibility catalyst: Kraken listing scheduled for Dec 19 with a 1:6 distribution ratio for Nov 11 snapshot holders. Communit...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Two parallel engineering threads: (1) a Polymarket tracking agent was built, writing bets into Neon and deployed to GitHub and Fly.io (next step: tighten conversational behavior), and (2) persistent l...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core developers compared AI-assisted development workflows (Cursor Opus, multi-instance prompting across machines), discussed virtualization/worktree/container strategies to manage parallel AI session...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-15</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-16.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-16.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community attention centered on AI16Z→ElizaOS token migration friction (notably Bithumb delays) and an urgent, unverified claim that the migration site was compromised and used to drain tokens. In parallel, engineering discussions emphasized cloud-platform rollout and quality/stability improvements (SQL fixes, auth foundations, and tighter PR validation expectations).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Unified API - serverless - nodejs (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;.eliza needed or plugin-sql crashes, should autocreate (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docs (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Primary thread: token migration delays (especially Bithumb/Korean users) and responsibility clarification (CEX-held tokens must be migrated by exchanges). A high-risk allegation emerged that the migra...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Engineering support focused on a DB failure mode where Twitter replies triggered foreign key constraint errors; a contributor suggested latest codebase includes SQL fixes. Additional help centered on ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Proposal to repurpose the partners channel into an 'Eliza-Alpha' preview channel for cloud demos/teasers, inviting strategic non-holders to test and amplify (especially if X access returns). A core me...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-14</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-15.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-15.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; elizaOS discussions centered on accelerating Eliza Cloud toward a full create→publish→monetize→promote loop (with SEO, ads, and social publishing integrations) while users surfaced practical friction around token migration via hardware wallets and plugin/config errors. GitHub activity (month-to-date) indicates heavy platform hardening plus major platform-enabling workstreams (cloud integration, unified API, and JWT-based multi-tenant auth).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Unified API - serverless - nodejs (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;.eliza needed or plugin-sql crashes, should autocreate (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Shaw reported Eliza Cloud is progressing toward rapid building of agents/apps/n8n workflows and MCP/A2A services, explicitly implementing a business loop (create→publish→monetize→promote) with new SEO...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users discussed migrating Ai16z tokens to ElizaOS using Ledger hardware wallets; a recurring issue is holdings not appearing when connecting Ledger directly. Community guidance recommends connecting L...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; A prior-day support thread indicates users encountered TEXT_LARGE errors even with minimal input; the likely cause was missing inference plugin registration (e.g., OpenAI), with outdated packages impl...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-13</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-14.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-14.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community focus split between immediate developer UX issues (missing AI plugin causing TEXT_LARGE errors; plugin install failures likely due to outdated packages) and broader ecosystem concerns (token migration issues on Bithumb and price anxiety) alongside ongoing platform hardening and major feature work (Cloud integration, TypeScript/build stabilization, JWT auth/multi-tenant direction).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: resolve TypeScript build errors in every packages - first step (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Add ElizaOS Cloud as Default AI Provider in CLI (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): migrate to messageService API and auto-create PGLite directories (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; A user reported TEXT_LARGE errors even for short prompts; root cause was identified as missing AI inference plugin registration (e.g., OpenAI). Follow-on OpenAI plugin install failures were attributed...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Mostly casual chat (memes/profile pictures) with minor product chatter: 'Kled app release' mentioned without details; a user suggested ElizaOS can interact with NFTs; brief MOCA reference; 'how to red...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; A brief mention of 'Business Eliza' suggests partner interest in a business-focused Eliza variant, but without implementation detail....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-13</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-13.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-13.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS community focused heavily on prediction markets and price betting mechanisms while developers addressed critical security vulnerabilities and implemented major authentication improvements. Technical discussions centered around hackathon opportunities and integration challenges with various APIs and payment systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users initiated prediction markets for ElizaOS token price betting, with DorianD proposing bets on whether ElizaOS would be above/below $0.01 by NYE. Discussion included time decay algorithms for bett...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical discussions focused on Twitter agent API consumption issues, data pipeline fixes for elizaOS/knowledge repository, and guidance on integrating x402 payment capabilities. Users also discussed...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Brief technical discussions about workflow alerts, security agent development sprint planning, and suggestions to reduce GitHub Discord webhook noise by filtering to important events only....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-11</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-12.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-12.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The day's intelligence is dominated by ElizaOS token migration issues, particularly affecting Korean users on Bithumb exchange, alongside core development progress including monorepo fixes and preparation for the Babylon web-based gaming platform launch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[DRAFT] feat(core): Implement parallel action execution in processActions (draft)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: resolve TypeScript build errors in every packages - first step (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Significant frustration among Korean users regarding the ELIZA token migration on Bithumb exchange, with team members acknowledging issues but indicating they're waiting on Bithumb. Users expressed co...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical discussions focused on ElizaOS deployment issues and integrations, particularly database connections (PGLite vs PostgreSQL), TypeScript build issues, and API integrations with Twitter and la...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Stan reported fixing critical issues in the monorepo (PR #6218) after Shaw's cleanup work broke types, tests, and try/catch blocks. Performance issues with pglite were noted (response times increasing...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-11</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-11.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-11.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; A critical security vulnerability was discovered in elizaOS allowing attackers to extract secrets via API endpoints, while ongoing plugin issues with SQL and Twitter components continue to affect users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): optimize pre-1.6.5 migration, RLS handling and SQL organisation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; A critical security vulnerability was discovered where server doesn't require ELIZA_SERVER_AUTH_TOKEN, allowing attackers to extract secrets via API endpoints. The issue stems from process.env being d...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Multiple users reported foreign key constraint errors with plugin-sql and plugin-twitter components when creating memories. Stan is working on a fix and migration guide. Users also discussed API optio...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion focused on Polymarket's marketing strategy using a 50 Cent song, targeting sports bettors and users who might identify with government scrutiny....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-10</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-10.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-10.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The ElizaOS ecosystem faces significant user frustration around the AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration process while development teams focus on code quality improvements and upcoming projects like ElizaOS Cloud, Babylon, and Jeju.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[DRAFT] feat(core): Implement parallel action execution in processActions (draft)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: enhance streaming support in text generation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Community members expressed significant frustration about the AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration process, which involved a sudden snapshot that caught holders off-guard. The token price is declining des...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Technical discussions focused on code quality improvements with Shaw submitting PR #6213 to fix types, remove unnecessary try/catch blocks, and clean up code. Future plans mentioned for "jeju" project...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Brief discussions about monetizing LLM models with x402 and Ollama, plus mentions of ROFL (Rust Optimized Fast Ledger) as potential technology for payment verification. Alchemy.com was recommended as ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-09</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-09.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-09.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; A critical security breach on the elizaOS.ai website was resolved, while development continues on significant features including parallel action execution, streaming functionality, and JWT authentication, amid user concerns about Twitter agent limitations and token price decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[DRAFT] feat(core): Implement parallel action execution in processActions (draft)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: enhance streaming support in text generation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: bump deps, fix drizzle-kit across ecosystem (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users expressed frustration about the ElizaOS token's continuous downtrend (approximately 40% in a month) while other cryptocurrencies recover. Significant discussion about Twitter agent functionality...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Brief technical discussions about extending PostgreSQL databases to work with ElizaOS's SQL plugin needs, with a GitHub code reference provided. A user also asked for recommendations on plugins to fet...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; A critical security incident was discovered and resolved where the elizaOS.ai website was compromised with an XMR cryptocurrency miner due to outdated Next.js dependencies with known RCE vulnerabiliti...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-08</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-08.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-08.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Development continues on core ElizaOS features including JWT authentication and parallel action execution, while users experience ongoing issues with the ai16z to ElizaOS token migration process that has prompted confusion and requests for clearer guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[DRAFT] feat(core): Implement parallel action execution in processActions (draft)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: bump deps, fix drizzle-kit across ecosystem (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;.eliza needed or plugin-sql crashes, should autocreate (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users continue experiencing issues with the ai16z to ElizaOS token migration process, with many reporting that their tokens aren't showing as eligible in the portal. Community members are directing us...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developer questions about implementing custom REST API endpoints in ElizaOS projects remained unanswered. A new developer with Sui ecosystem and Move language experience introduced themselves to the c...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; GitHub pull request #6210 was shared in the channel, though no technical details were discussed....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-07</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-07.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-07.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS continues token migration from AI16Z with user confusion and technical issues reported, while development progresses on ElizaCloud and parallel action execution architecture (PR #6209), alongside a new decentralized OTC desk announcement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[DRAFT] feat(core): Implement parallel action execution in processActions (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add ElizaOS Cloud as Default AI Provider in CLI (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(cli): correct startAgents API signature in e2e-tests (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users continue to experience confusion about the AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration process, with technical issues including 'Max Amount Reached' errors. Terminological debates about 'hard fork vs. migr...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; ElizaCloud release timeline was discussed with only a vague 'soon(tm)' response provided. A user suggested designing products with power users in mind, as most revenue will come from highly engaged us...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Developers discussed a draft PR (#6209) for implementing parallel execution of actions, which would optimize processing time while maintaining the integrity of dependent action sequences....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-06</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-06.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-06.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS development is focused on streaming support implementation and security enhancements, while the community deals with ongoing token migration issues and scam attempts requiring vigilant monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Streaming Support (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;.eliza needed or plugin-sql crashes, should autocreate (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users are discussing migration from AI16Z to ElizaOS with mixed sentiments about price impact. Several users need help with token migration, particularly those who purchased tokens after the snapshot....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Stan is working on unifying the `useModel` behavior for both normal and streaming modes, starting with plugin-openrouter before extending to plugin-openai and plugin-anthropic. PR #20 for plugin-openr...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; A user named 'ninja' requested an elegant Python solution for an admin plugin to reset admin access without requiring a restart after using the unlock phrase, but no solution was provided....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-05</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-05.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-05.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS is facing token migration issues affecting Korean exchanges while core developers are working to simplify the developer experience with the framework and continue development of upcoming products including Babylon platform, ElizaCloud, and Otako.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;.eliza needed or plugin-sql crashes, should autocreate (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): migrate to messageService API and auto-create PGLite directories (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(service): enhance simple response detection logic (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Unified API - serverless - nodejs (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Significant issues with the AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration, particularly affecting Korean exchanges like Bithumb and Coinone. The Digital Asset eXchange Alliance (DAXA) has placed AI16Z under an "In...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core developers identified significant usability issues with the ElizaOS framework, noting that creating a basic agent requires excessive boilerplate code. Stan proposed an ElizaOS wrapper class to si...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion about Anthropic's revenue growth, potential IPO, and competition from Chinese model providers. Speculative conversation about viral features for AI agents, including social connection track...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-04</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-04.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-04.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Token migration from ai16z to elizaOS is causing significant user confusion and technical challenges, while core development continues with authentication improvements and API standardization through new PRs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Unified API - serverless - nodejs (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users are experiencing significant issues with the ai16z to elizaOS token migration process, especially those with tokens on exchanges like Bithumb and Kraken which have paused trading. Scammers are t...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Ongoing negotiations with Twitter (X) for social media restoration are being slowed by "Musk's legal legacy". There's interest in creating dashboard analytics similar to Zama's Dune dashboard, and dis...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Stan is implementing a "plugin-waitlist" concept proposed by Odilitime and has submitted two PRs (#6200 and #6201) to the elizaOS/eliza repository. Former team members Loaf and Galego have created a n...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-03</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-03.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-03.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The ElizaOS ecosystem is experiencing significant developments in token migration (AI16Z to ElizaOS with 6:1 conversion), technical improvements (streaming functionality, plugin memory architecture, authentication enhancements), and business model planning (potential marketplace with revenue sharing for developers).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(server): optimization and reorganization (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(client): improve markdown content spacing (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Populate "Community Agents" or Remove Section (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove "Quick Presets" from Generation Studio (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add "$" symbol to Credit Balances (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Extensive discussions on AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration (6:1 ratio), with mixed sentiment about price performance. Kraken exchange announced pausing AI16Z trading while evaluating migration support....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical discussions about ElizaOS implementation, using Deepseek as a provider through openrouter plugin, and troubleshooting agent connection issues. Concerns raised about the high cost of X (Twitt...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion about ElizaCloud's potential business model, with suggestions for a marketplace similar to Salesforce AppExchange/Apple App Store with 30% platform revenue cut and standardized URL structur...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-02</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-02.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-02.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Development focus on server optimization and markdown rendering improvements, while community discussions center on AI business models, particularly monetization strategies for brand-specific agents and enterprise implementation challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(server): optimization and reorganization (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(client): improve markdown content spacing (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: markdown spacing compact (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[Server] Concurrent connection timeouts &amp; add reliability patterns (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where did packages/docs/ go? (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users discussed potential business applications for AI agents, particularly in marketing and sales contexts, with monetization strategies like lead generation for high-ticket items, brand-specific age...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Blockchain developers introduced themselves, and a user reported a technical issue with the ElizaOS Discord plugin (TypeError: "this.runtime.hasElizaOS is not a function"), which Odilitime acknowledge...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; DorianD shared the "Official Lean AI Company Playbook" from Substack, emphasizing AI implementation in non-technical departments like accounting, customer experience, and marketing, suggesting ElizaOS...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-01</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-01.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-01.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS development is focusing on multi-user authentication implementation and architecture clarification, while the community discusses Babylon release timeline estimations and token migration issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Voice Support (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile App (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Standardize Logging Across Core, CLI, and Server (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;rollback(plugin-sql): revert build configuration changes (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core developers are working on implementing JSON Web Key Sets (JWKs) providers as part of a multi-user authentication sprint, with a pull request nearly ready that implements 'mostly every JWKs provid...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Discussions clarified that ElizaOS is primarily designed for single-user operation, with multi-user implementations requiring additional development work. Users were advised to examine Otaku and Spart...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Community members speculated about Babylon's release timeline (estimates ranging from weeks to January), with over 206,000 users already signed up. Users also reported difficulties swapping AI16Z to E...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-11-30</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-11-30.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-11-30.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The day's intelligence centers on the ongoing AI16z to ElizaOS token migration process with numerous user inquiries and technical discussions, alongside development of mobile implementations for elizaOS and significant GitHub activity focused on security improvements and bug fixes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;rollback(plugin-sql): revert build configuration changes (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: dynamic prompt normalization follow-up (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Entity-level RLS &amp; Security Improvements (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users are actively discussing the AI16z to ElizaOS token migration process, seeking help with status checks and reporting scam attempts. Community moderators are directing users to appropriate support...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical discussion focused on Endless's attempt to run elizaOS on Android devices using Termux with proot, with the main challenge being getting the Bun JavaScript runtime working on mobile. The use...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; DorianD dominated conversation with observations about cryptocurrency trends, migration to Farcaster, and suggestions for comprehensive cross-platform distribution strategies for Eliza Labs content in...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-11-29</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-11-29.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-11-29.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS is focused on managing token migration issues while development activity shows minimal GitHub commits but significant strategic planning for entity-level security, improved user interfaces, and payment system expansions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multi-asset charts (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Entity-level RLS &amp; Security Improvements (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: dynamic prompt normalization follow-up (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; The channel is primarily focused on token migration issues with users seeking clarification on the manual migration process, particularly for those who provided liquidity during the snapshot period. U...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Brief discussion about Hyperliquid (HL) taking fees away from centralized exchanges like Binance rather than from Ethereum, with observations that successful L1 blockchains should focus on taking user...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion about marketing strategy improvements including newsletters, blog posts, social media presence, community programs, and regular meetups. Suggestions to expand user interviews into broader m...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-11-28</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-11-28.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-11-28.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS is focused on token migration and exchange support issues while making technical improvements to security with Entity-level Row Level Security (RLS) and bug fixes for logging, prompts, and Discord plugin functionality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: dynamic prompt normalization follow-up (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Entity-level RLS &amp; Security Improvements (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users are seeking updates on token migration/rebranding process, particularly for Bithumb and Kraken exchanges. The team confirms they're coordinating with Kraken's communications team, though no spec...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Technical discussion focused on Discord plugin bug fixes, logging improvements, and tool routing systems. Issues with the 'gpt-5-nano' model were identified and fixed, requiring 'max_completion_tokens...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion about who was responsible for an unannounced snapshot related to migration, SAFT agreements with new investors, and partner role verification issues in Discord. Team mentioned elizaOS might...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
