<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="style.xsl"?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>elizaOS Daily Intelligence</title>
    <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge</link>
    <description>Daily facts and insights from the elizaOS ecosystem</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 02:25:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/rss/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <ns0:link href="https://x.com/elizaos" rel="related" title="@elizaos on X"/>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/rss.xml" rel="related" title="GitHub Activity Feed"/>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-04</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-06.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-06.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community discussions focused on agent architecture (multi-model setups, RoseOS framework) and operational bottlenecks (Turbo build memory usage, plugin versioning). In parallel, GitHub activity emphasized platform reliability/UX fixes and ongoing plugin security/performance work (notably Twitter OAuth2 PKCE and improved OpenAI media handling).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): use sql.raw() for SET LOCAL to avoid parameterization… (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(default-message-service): optimize provider handling in MultiStep (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work started on OAuth2 PKCE authentication flow (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix image descriptions and add caching for audio/image handlers (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add community plugin `plugin-coinrailz` to registry (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;overall:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion included RoseOS (a framework on ElizaOS), multi-model agent setups using Openrouter/provider configuration, guidance to deploy agents with custom plugins via cloud containers using the Eliz...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;overall:&lt;/em&gt; Updates included continued DegenAI development, progress on Eliza knowledge data pipelines with upcoming documentation/presentation, and Polymarket Phase 2 repository updates. Technical trading discus...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-05</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-05.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-05.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion and development activity centered on improving agent reliability and operability (logging standards, faster multi-provider execution, and data-isolation DB correctness) while expanding deployment/model-provider flexibility (OpenRouter multi-model setups, cloud container deployments). Product work and requests emphasized public-agent UX states, message limits for anonymous users, and higher-quality chat summaries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): use sql.raw() for SET LOCAL to avoid parameterizatio… (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(default-message-service): optimize provider handling in MultiStep (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chore(license): update year to 2026 (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chat summaries don't really make much sense. Can we improve (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Limit messages for non-signed up user to ~2-3 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#general:&lt;/em&gt; Key discussion topics included multi-model agent setups using OpenRouter configuration, deploying agents (including custom plugins) via cloud containers, and recent logging improvements attributed to ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-03</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-04.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-04.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion and development updates centered on ElizaOS as a composable agent framework, with active guidance on multi-model agent setups and cloud container deployments. On the engineering side, provider execution was optimized, logging standards were reinforced with a linter, and GitHub activity included a SQL plugin fix plus new UX issues filed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(default-message-service): optimize provider handling in MultiStep (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): use sql.raw() for SET LOCAL to avoid parameterization issues (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scroll should work on whole page (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connect wallet should ideally go straight to wallet options (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation included high-level positioning of ElizaOS as an open-source framework for autonomous agents ('Linux' analogy) and an introduction of roseOS as an experimental framework built on ElizaOS ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical guidance focused on configuring multi-model agents (e.g., Anthropic and OpenAI together) using the Openrouter plugin with env-defined providers, and deploying agents with custom plugins via ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core dev discussion noted improved logging work tied to PR #6263 and a new log-format linter in eliza/config intended to be integrated across projects and plugins; a separate thread shared an 'agentic...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-02</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-03.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-03.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Activity centered on UX and access-control changes for public agents (message limits, public agent UI states, improved summaries) alongside continued community friction around AI16z→ElizaOS token migration and wallet compatibility. Core-dev discussion referenced ongoing PR review work (streaming-related) and plugin development (plugin-github updates and a new plugin-git).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change free credits from $5 to $1 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public agent cards should have chat number (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Separate public agent states (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Limit messages for non-signed up user to ~2-3 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chat summaries don't really make much sense. Can we improve (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation included token migration questions and wallet issues (reports of tokens not showing after transfers to Phantom), plus a brief redirection of an NFT smart contract question to the coders c...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Community discussed contributing and plugins; an unanswered question asked whether an entire GitHub codebase could be imported as an agent, and Odilitime shared the plugin-github repo while noting ong...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; DorianD proposed an AI 'cost reduction and migration agent' to analyze AWS usage and migrate workloads to cheaper alternatives, referencing the VersusControl/ai-infrastructure-agent project....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-01</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-02.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-02.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion centered on agentic game development (a RuneScape fork aiming for a “Zelda with agents” experience) and required features for Hyperscape tooling, alongside recurring community questions about token migration, token contract details, and token utility/integration with cloud services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critical fix to ensure streaming LLM calls are properly logged to the database (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modernize CLI toolchain to use Bun-native processes (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Standardize internal server communication routes (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add core support for Chain-of-Thought (CoT) reasoning (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refactor the internal messaging system / messaging API redesign (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation was dominated by New Year greetings plus repeated questions about token contract details and migration from AI16Z to ElizaOS; a roadmap question was answered with the GitHub roadmap link,...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; A new member joined referencing Shaw; Kenk asked whether Eliza can be used to manage and schedule Farcaster posts, with no answer captured in the provided segment....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core-dev discussion focused on an agentic game concept: forking a RuneScape project into a Zelda-like experience where Eliza agents (and Spartan) populate towns and generate quests; Shaw listed missin...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-31</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-01.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-01.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Work centered on Jeju Network backend progress (including an OAuth3 testnet nameserver routed via on-chain registry to IPFS), continued preparation for Cloud/Babylon launches, and ongoing ElizaOS token migration logistics. Community discussions also covered DegenAI’s 1M-token autotrader gating, documentation gaps around token info, and wallet/migration support issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure streaming LLM calls are properly logged to the database (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Standardize internal server message routes (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix image descriptions and introduce caching for audio and image handlers (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement OAuth2 PKCE authentication flow (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add community-created plugin-coinrailz to the registry (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion included migration and chain availability questions (BSC and Solana), DegenAI’s 1M-token autotrader gating and referenced stack partners (Chainlink, Cambrian), and user reports of Phantom d...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Jin described an image pipeline that generates art from summarized Discord/GitHub activity with date-based seasonal variance and a goal of newspaper-style visuals; an additional report mentioned an un...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Shaw mentioned migrating infrastructure to run on Jeju in preparation for going public after launching Cloud and Babylon; discussion also included speculative market commentary (capital rotation; debt...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-30</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-31.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-31.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community activity centered on a reported ~120% $elizaOS price move following Shaw regaining access to X and discussing Jeju infrastructure plans. In parallel, engineering work progressed on unified hooks (multi-transport) and streaming LLM logging fixes, while users continued to seek clarity and support for the AI16Z→ElizaOS migration and token information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unified hooks with multi-transport support (HTTP/SSE/WebSocket) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(core): log streaming LLM calls to database (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;saftey → safety (typo fix) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My agent cards resizing to match dashboard agent cards (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unslop Apps (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users discussed the reported ~$elizaOS price move tied to Shaw returning to X, asked migration questions about AI16Z→ElizaOS, and requested clearer token information and role verification processes (e...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Builders shared agent-development resources (skills repo and OpenSouls integration), discussed Twitter API cost constraints ($200/month), and exchanged implementation details for embedding ElizaCloud ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Shaw described Jeju’s infrastructure plan (AWS first, then self-owned racks). Kenk noted tokenomics documentation updates and short-term plans to add CoinGecko links; documentation requests included a...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-29</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-30.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-30.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS community attention centered on the project and Shaw returning to X (Twitter) and an associated large Twitter Space, while product work continued with Eliza Cloud open beta, cross-chain token availability, and multiple merged GitHub improvements. Ongoing friction remained around the AI16Z→ElizaOS migration process and a set of developer-facing setup/UX bugs reported in Discord.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(server): standardize message server route naming (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs(plugin-dummy-services): add comprehensive README (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(cli): replace execa and child_process with Bun.spawn and bun-exec utilities (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs: fix documentation inconsistencies and add missing test flags (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When clicking on agent, if it has at least one conversation, open that conversation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Community discussion included confirmation of new agents released to production, cross-chain token availability, migration snapshot completion, Eliza Cloud beta availability, contract-address sharing,...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developer support questions focused on Windows setup issues for a DaVinci Resolve MCP integration (Python import error) and an unresolved error when chatting with an agent via share link....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core development discussion included review needs for PR #6285, a docs PR (#81) for Cloud integration and monorepo coverage, a proposed Branded UUIDs PR, Discord plugin PR #36 logging improvements (ch...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-28</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-29.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-29.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Core developers discussed a decentralized cloud marketplace running on Jeju and Babylon, framed as an on-chain alternative to Vercel with integrated DNS, caching, and database components. In parallel, migration usability issues and ecosystem/affiliation confusion continued to generate user support load.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snapshot Eligibility Issue + Tangem Wallet Connection Not Supported (Discord Support Compromised) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users asked for clarification about which projects are officially affiliated with elizaOS (e.g., Zora) and reported migration issues including wallet connection and token exchange problems; multiple u...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; A brief exchange referenced a trading bot and mentioned complexity-science informed Bayesian inference, without sharing implementation details....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Shaw announced cloud services running on Jeju and Babylon and described a decentralized Vercel-like compute marketplace including agents/inference, DNS/domain purchasing, distributed cache, and a SQLi...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-27</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-28.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-28.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion centered on AI16Z→ElizaOS migration constraints and unresolved tokenomics questions, alongside engineering updates including the proposed “jeju” distributed cloud platform and multiple ElizaCloud usability/validation bugs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snapshot Eligibility Issue + Tangem Wallet Connection Not Supported (Discord Support Compromised) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Add ElizaOS Cloud as Default AI Provider in CLI (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: enhance streaming support in text generation (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users requested Eliza Cloud API endpoint information (answered as available on the site), asked about migration limits, and discussed identifying projects as built on “elizaos cloud” for distribution....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Bug reports included agent-name validation failures (“null” and numeric names causing exceptions) and a deployment failure involving ECR credentials/repository discovery when using `elizaos deploy`. U...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Migration policy was reiterated: only snapshot-held tokens can be migrated and post-snapshot purchases are excluded. DorianD asked whether ElizaOS will be Jeju’s native token; Borko responded that tok...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-26</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-27.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-27.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS Cloud officially launched and immediately saw community agent-building activity, alongside active engineering work on streaming, workflows, and authentication improvements. In parallel, Discord discussions centered on token price drawdown and lingering friction from the AI16Z→ElizaOS migration, including exchange-related concerns and requests for clearer token utility documentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhance multi-step workflow with retry logic and parameter extraction capabilities (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Standardize naming conventions for message server routes (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion focused on the project’s transition from AI16Z meme coin roots to utility, token drawdown (90–98% from ATH), migration friction (snapshot-based eligibility and exchange confusion), and the ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developers discussed Cloud/agent technical issues (deployment username-null error, file uploads, Ollama model configuration) and tooling constraints (bun required; npm not supported). A workaround for...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Jeju Network questions centered on decentralization goals (confirmed as core) and an unanswered question on whether Jeju’s token will be $elizaos; a previously mentioned “life-changing event” expected...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-25</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-26.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-26.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion centered on the AI16Z→ElizaOS token migration, ongoing price decline, and exchange-support risk, while the team continued positioning Eliza Cloud as the primary near-term tokenomics/value-accrual mechanism. Development and roadmap work continued in parallel, including Cloud beta onboarding and upcoming mainnet milestones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snapshot Eligibility Issue + Tangem Wallet Connection Not Supported (Discord Support Compromised) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation focused on migration eligibility (Nov 11 snapshot wallet requirement), token mintability for Chainlink CCIP, migration rationale (moving off token2022 for exchange compatibility), token u...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Participants compared ElizaOS FDV (~$22M) to competitors (Pippin, Virtuals), discussed communication expectations, and reiterated that Cloud rollout is tied to implementing tokenomics....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Shaw proposed splitting Babylon into points and non-points components, with the points game using Eliza Cloud for inference/authentication and a stated target of migrating 350,000 users; discussion al...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-24</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-25.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-25.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion centered on ElizaOS token value accrual and how Eliza Cloud revenue will be used, alongside near-term Cloud feature clarifications (upload limits, planned custom model hosting). Development updates emphasized documentation cleanup, plugin work (including Starknet), and CI reliability issues tied to Claude billing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monorepo documentation needs fixing (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problems with spacing in numbered items (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conversation duplication bug (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opening agent chat should show most recent conversation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation focused on tokenomics and value accrual; team clarified that Eliza Cloud revenue (not yield) will be used for token buybacks, with further token utility planned for the Jeju release. Migr...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developer-focused discussion included plugin-starknet updates and guidance on building knowledge-backed agents in ElizaOS Cloud, including a 50MB upload limit, Markdown preference, and planned custom ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Debate on tokenomics compared ElizaOS to Virtual’s pairing model; team response emphasized token value tied to product usage and infrastructure development. Unusual sell patterns were discussed with s...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-23</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-24.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-24.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Eliza Cloud entered beta with ecosystem builders being onboarded ahead of a planned January ramp-up, while the team prepared for an 8004 mainnet milestone in mid-January and an agent onboarding push before EthDenver. In parallel, Discord discussions continued to center on ELIZAOS token utility/price concerns and near-term technical cleanup (plugin message standardization, analytics, and plugin fixes).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proposal to add a feedback button to the application. (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementation of chat renaming functionality. (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Addressing streaming and state management in the application. (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A request to update the Brandkit on GitHub. (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improves message service handlers to perform asynchronous operations and optimizes them for cloud platforms. (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Eliza Cloud was announced as entering beta with ecosystem builders being onboarded for production feedback; a January ramp-up plan (PR, launch event, coding influencers) and a mid-January 8004 mainnet...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core dev status updates included: a fix for streaming issues in cloud build mode, Discord plugin fixes, ongoing work on EPIC 5 items, a pending PR to standardize Elizaos.handleMessage across plugins, ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Brief discussion mentioned a community project (GAMEBORO, an AI gaming assistant on Steam) and shared metrics for elizaos and degenai....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-22</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-23.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-23.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community discussion centered on ELIZAOS token utility/price concerns alongside imminent product delivery, with the team emphasizing the near-term launch of Eliza Cloud and planned buybacks/airdrops. Technical threads focused on a Starknet plugin deployment error, interoperability strategy proposals, and a surfaced high-severity n8n RCE vulnerability reference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create Agent Button should be same in My Agents and Dashboard (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move avatar button to #4 in agent builder (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add Topics/Adjectives to form (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inline send message button (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tooltip for system prompt (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Token utility and price decline dominated, alongside repeated explanations that Eliza Cloud is near launch and that Cloud revenue will fund buybacks; ecosystem projects Babylon and Otako were cited as...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; A Starknet plugin 'unruggable' deployment flow failed with a String-to-BigInt parsing error; Odilitime requested the modified unruggable.ts for debugging. The suspended main X account and alternate ac...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; A brief market-structure note stated there are more sellers than buyers and referenced weak AI-crypto sector performance as context for price action....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-20</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-22.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-22.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community discussion centered on token price performance and ongoing ai16z→elizaOS migration constraints, while the team prepared to ship an ElizaOS Cloud MVP with streaming capabilities. Parallel GitHub work emphasized stability (migrations, security fixes), streaming foundations, plugin ecosystem expansion, and UX/onboarding planning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): optimize pre-1.6.5 migration, RLS handling and SQL organisation (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: encryption for character secrets in correct order (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Add ElizaOS Cloud as Default AI Provider in CLI (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add self-hosted Farcaster plugin to registry (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement unified messaging API (plugin-telegram) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#elizaos:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion included concerns about elizaOS token price behavior, confusion about ai16z→elizaOS migration (including eligibility constraints), confirmation of a signed X (Twitter) deal, and product upd...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#elizaos:&lt;/em&gt; Migration deadline details (Feb 4, 2026) were reiterated, with clarification that ai16z is tradable but has no utility and elizaOS is the supported path. Technical coordination for cloud streaming was...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-20</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-21.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-21.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community focus centered on ElizaOS token price weakness and ongoing AI16Z→ELIZAOS migration confusion, alongside heightened scam/impersonation risk. The team signaled near-term product momentum (Cloud MVP shipping Monday, v1.7.0 streaming release) and a business milestone (deal signed with X), with promises of token utility and buybacks plus a Q1/Q2 2026 roadmap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The SQL plugin was enhanced to ensure smooth data migration for users updating from older versions (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A test failure in the CLI was resolved to improve reliability of the development environment (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI improvements to make plugin selection more intuitive (toggle selection / visual feedback) (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI improvements to make plugin selection more intuitive (toggle selection / visual feedback) (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redesigned dashboard planning (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Dominant themes were token price decline, confusion/anger around the AI16Z→ELIZAOS migration (including AI16Z pumping despite deprecation), and repeated scam-link warnings. A team member indicated Clo...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Brief updates/links highlighted the v1.7.0 release (streaming + npm fixes), discussion comparing the tool to Playwright/Puppeteer (embedded approach), request for TradingView chart integration, and mi...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Only a single post sharing the v1.7.0 GitHub release link; no discussion....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-19</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-20.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-20.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Primary themes were continued community friction around the AI16Z→elizaOS token migration (deadline set for 2026-02-04) and a near-term engineering push to ship cloud streaming, alongside ongoing work on EVM/onchain capabilities and ecosystem analytics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: bootstrap action/provide format change fix + initPromise fix (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize Agent Builder Model Selection (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow JSON export without deploying (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rename chat assistant to "Agent Builder" (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix markdown bullet point rendering (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation was dominated by token migration status and sentiment: elizaOS positioned as the only utility-forward token, AI16Z still tradable but without utility, and a firm migration deadline of 202...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developers discussed onchain/EVM support maturity: concerns about plugin-evm maintenance, ongoing EVM support work for Spartan, and an updated “knowledge repository” exposing JSON endpoints (leaderboa...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core team outlined release sequencing for cloud streaming: release monorepo → review/merge elizacloud-plugin → update cloud-v2 to latest core. They also noted NPM token changes breaking releases (clas...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-18</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-19.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-19.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Engineering effort centered on improving agent messaging/streaming and provider performance (parallelization + timeouts), while ecosystem work highlighted Starknet plugin integration breakages. Community discourse was dominated by token migration/exchange confusion and negative sentiment over price/perceived delivery gaps, alongside a notable Hyperfy v0.16.0 release announcement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: enhance streaming support in text generation (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(default-message-service): optimize provider handling in MultiStep (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: bootstrap action/provide format change fix + initPromise fix (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;remove reassign runtime.db to individual connection (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docs (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation was dominated by negative community sentiment: complaints about token price decline, perceived lack of product delivery, and a contentious AI16Z→ELIZAOS migration described as confusing/d...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Starknet plugin integration troubleshooting: questions on correct plugin installation approach, widespread TypeScript type mismatches (AgentRuntime vs IAgentRuntime) across action files, and a runtime...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core discussion centered on provider performance architecture: PR #6263 proposes parallel provider execution with configurable timeout (default 1s) and warnings for slow providers, with debate on enfo...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-17</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-18.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-18.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Primary themes were continued friction and confusion around the AI16Z→ELIZAOS migration (especially exchange-specific handling and Korean community concerns), alongside ongoing core product work (streaming, plugin actions) and process pressure to merge an oversized Discord plugin PR. GitHub signals strong near-term prioritization of UI/UX simplification (terminology cleanups, edit-mode behavior fixes) and platform stability work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix edit mode chat suggestions triggering agent responses (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix avatar mismatch between edit view and sidebar (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Replace "RAG" terminology with plain language (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snapshot Eligibility Issue + Tangem Wallet Connection Not Supported (Discord Support Compromised) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation was dominated by token migration confusion and frustration (notably Korean community concerns about Bithumb) and discrepancies in how exchanges (e.g., Bithumb vs Kraken) treat snapshot-ba...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developers discussed extending agent actions in a Starknet plugin context: suggested cloning the plugin into the monorepo packages folder, adding new action files under actions, and registering them v...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; A business/deployment signal emerged: market makers reportedly want agents deployed in production and visibly engaging in social environments before committing further; emphasis was placed on iteratin...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
