<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="style.xsl"?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>elizaOS Daily Intelligence</title>
    <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge</link>
    <description>Daily facts and insights from the elizaOS ecosystem</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 08:09:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/rss/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <ns0:link href="https://x.com/elizaos" rel="related" title="@elizaos on X"/>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/rss.xml" rel="related" title="GitHub Activity Feed"/>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-20</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-20.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-20.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS released version 1.7.2 focusing on stability and streaming reliability, while core development shifted toward a Rust-based v2.0.0 and WASM compatibility. Community discussions centered on AI-powered moderation systems and market liquidity cycles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;V2.0.0 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(v2.0.0): wasm agent runtime (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dashboard usability bug: clicking outside input box (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Community discussed Quantitative Easing cycles and their positive historical impact on crypto microcaps, alongside concerns over long-term token sustainability....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#coders:&lt;/em&gt; Demonstration of 'Solimp', an Eliza-based Telegram moderation bot using exponential mutes to manage spam. Discussion also covered the 'jintern' revival and development of RAG systems using the knowled...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Technical review of PR #6286 focused on refining 'ensureEntities' logic into batch processing rather than individual calls to optimize runtime performance....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-19</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-19.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-19.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Core development remains focused on the v2.0.0 Rust/TypeScript transition and significant database refactoring, while the community faces anxiety regarding token utility, budget constraints, and price manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(plugin-sql): extract domain stores from BaseDrizzleAdapter (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(v2.0.0): wasm agent runtime (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reflection evaluator fails with 'Entity not found' (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Initiative launched to optimize technical documentation specifically for AI agent consumption using kapa.ai's best practices....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Deep concerns regarding token performance and utility; debate on the future of AI-integrated prediction markets....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-18</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-18.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-18.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Development shifted towards ElizaOS v2.0.0 with significant infrastructure refactoring, alongside the successful implementation of Eliza on the Internet Computer Protocol (ICP). Community attention is currently focused on the February 4th token migration deadline and technical hurdles in prediction market integrations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(plugin-sql): extract domain stores from BaseDrizzleAdapter (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;V2.0.0 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;USE_OPENAI_EMBEDDING setting not respected (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Debates on the validity of AI prediction markets and proposals for holder rewards tied to agent creation....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical deep dive into high-performance trading systems using Rust and NATS Jetstream; troubleshooting Cloudflare 403 blocks on Polymarket CLOB APIs....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#partners:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion of the Jeju decentralized compute network and its potential use for asynchronous autonomous agents....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-17</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-17.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-17.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS development has reached a stable milestone with significant performance optimizations in runtime initialization and the refactoring of core database adapters. However, the project faces critical community challenges including token price manipulation by whales and a sophisticated GitHub repository spoofing incident involving manipulated Git commits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(plugin-sql): extract domain stores from BaseDrizzleAdapter (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(v2.0.0): wasm agent runtime (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reflection evaluator fails with 'Entity not found' - UPDATE_CONTACT requires entity initialization (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Intense discussion on token economics, whale manipulation ($2M sell-off), and the verification of Git commits via PGP signatures following repo spoofing....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#coders:&lt;/em&gt; Deep dive into high-performance Solana infrastructure including gRPC streaming and Jito's ShredStream; clarification that automated trading on Polymarket is officially supported....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-16</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-16.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-16.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS is prioritizing architectural simplification in version 2.0.0 and cloud refinement while managing a critical token migration deadline on February 4th. Development highlights include the release of a Polymarket trading plugin and significant core performance optimizations in agent initialization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;V2.0.0 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(plugin-sql): extract domain stores from BaseDrizzleAdapter (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Dominance of token migration support for users encountering Phantom and Trust wallet errors; community concern regarding significant market price decline....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical deep dive into Polymarket API legitimacy, Socket.IO server access patterns for custom plugins, and Together.ai inference integration....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-15</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-15.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-15.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Error: Failed to generate briefing due to LLM or parsing issues.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-14</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-14.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-14.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The core development team has pivoted focus to ElizaCloud improvements, de-prioritizing v2.0.0 work. Significant technical progress was made in multi-step workflows while the project addressed critical OAuth infrastructure planning and GitHub Action authentication failures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(v2.0.0): wasm agent runtime (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;V2.0.0 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messaging API - Fix double processing &amp; align transports (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Focus has shifted to ElizaCloud improvements including credit top-up idempotency fixes and test architecture review. Authentication issues with GitHub OIDC persist....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;coders:&lt;/em&gt; Discussions on Recursive Language Models (RLMs) for extended context and detailed instructions for monorepo knowledge uploads involving cli linking....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://cdn.elizaos.news/elizaos-media/embed-image-1460738683669053626_c1721f01.jpg" type="image/png" length="0"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-13</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-13.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-13.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS development focused on critical ElizaCloud app creator debugging and core performance optimizations, while community discussions centered on token value tied to the upcoming Jeju network. Infrastructure stability was addressed by resolving expired API keys in CI/CD pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: add plugin-blockrun for x402 micropayments (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: unified hooks with multi-transport support (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(plugin-sql): add CachedDatabaseAdapter with LRU caching (draft)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Extensive debate on token value; DorianD argued value is organic and depends on the Jeju network operationalizing gas fees for agents rather than VC-backed pumps....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical deep-dive on ElizaCloud app creator bugs including file visibility intermittently failing and git state corruption from manual AI agent commands....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Resolved expired Anthropic API keys in CI; discussed Rust runtime for performance, concluding Bun provides similar speed with lower overhead for current bottleneck areas....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-12</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-12.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-12.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Initial intelligence indicates significant performance benchmarks for ElizaOS, with core runtime initialization speed increased by up to 40%. Concurrently, development is pivoting toward decentralized infrastructure with the Jeju layer and a transition to Eliza 2.0 multi-language support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;V2.0.0 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;optimize runtime initialization (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;add plugin-blockrun for x402 micropayments (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Demonstration of 3D model/avatar generation with low poly mode; clarification that agent design uses separate human simulator components rather than subagents....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Debates regarding crypto adoption timelines (50+ years) and strategies for separating political content from project social media accounts....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-11</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-11.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-11.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The ecosystem is currently transitioning toward Eliza 2.0 and the Jeju Layer 2 launch, focusing on multi-language support and LLM-free agent architectures. While technical progress in gaming automation and cloud infrastructure is robust, the project faces significant headwinds from Korean exchange delistings and community debate over token utility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: add plugin-blockrun for x402 micropayments (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;V2.0.0 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;docs: core documentation guides (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Focus on the launch of Jeju layer and branding debates regarding 'Eliza Open Systems.' Significant concerns were raised about token price pressure due to contributor minting without active gas utility...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Showcasing of Rust implementations and LLM-free architectures. Stan and Shaw collaborated on MMO automation techniques, including evading bot detection in WoW using pixel encoding....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-10</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-10.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-10.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The ElizaOS ecosystem is undergoing a major architectural shift with the proposal of Eliza 2.0 while facing a regulatory crisis in South Korea as exchanges delist tokens. Development focus remains on cross-platform skill interoperability, cloud infrastructure billing, and the introduction of an MMORPG-style character progression system for the leaderboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;V2.0.0 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MMORPG-style character system to leaderboard API (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Discussions focused on Eliza 2.0 redesign and an experiment to convert plugins into deterministic 'skills' for cross-platform compatibility....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Contextualized the name 'JEJU' as a tech testing ground in Korea and explored AI applications for monitoring dopamine levels....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-09</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-09.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-09.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS faces a regulatory crisis as major Korean exchanges announce token delistings, while the development team prepares for a massive architectural shift with the Eliza 2.0 multi-language runtime proposal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;V2.0.0 (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: plugin-bootstrap (+ sql minor) actions/providers for serverId =&gt; messageServerId change (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Heavy focus on the Korean exchange delisting crisis and technical issues regarding the AI16Z token migration eligibility....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Discussions on Eliza 2.0 architecture, interoperability through plugin-to-skill conversion, and optimizing workflow orchestration....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-08</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-08.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-08.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The ElizaOS ecosystem is managing critical version 1.7.0 compatibility issues with the Discord plugin while facing significant delisting actions from major Korean exchanges. Development has pivoted towards architectural scaling via event pumps and a decentralized marketplace called Bazaar on the Jeju Layer 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: plugin-bootstrap (+ sql minor) actions/providers for serverId =&gt; messageServerId change (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): skip pgcrypto extension for PGLite (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chat Box UI Improvement - Dynamic Sizing (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Heavy focus on addressing Discord bot 'No server ID found' errors and reacting to Korean exchange delistings....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Technical planning for connector gateways and transition from simple event pumps to multi-daemon scaling for high-bandwidth voice connections....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-07</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-07.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-07.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The development team is prioritizing critical bug fixes for ElizaOS v1.7.0, specifically addressing Discord integration failures and database migration errors while initiating major performance optimizations for cloud infrastructure. Concurrently, a significant documentation overhaul and a strategic shift toward 'skills-based' plugin architecture are underway to improve developer onboarding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: plugin-bootstrap (+ sql minor) actions/providers for serverId =&gt; messageServerId change (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turbo build memory consumption &gt; 21GB (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Deep focus on Discord plugin troubleshooting, DegenAI development status, and clarifying token migration snapshot dates....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Architecture discussions regarding event pump scaling for voice connections and fixing TOCTOU race conditions in cloud agent credit deduction....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-06</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-06.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-06.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The ElizaOS ecosystem is transitioning into a stabilization phase, characterized by extensive documentation expansion and critical infrastructure fixes for SQL and MCP integrations. While core development progresses with ERC-8004 finalization, significant technical debt remains regarding build-time memory consumption and Discord server-detection bugs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;unified hooks with multi-transport support (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performance Concerns (Memory Consumption) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critical Publishing Failure Investigation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Community members debated the philosophy of the agent economy, contrasting ElizaOS's open-source ethos against closed-loop systems like Virtuals....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical deep dive into MCP server integration; revealed that Anthropic models require an OpenAI API key (even invalid) for text embedding fallbacks....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Focus on security maintenance through API key rotation and standardizing ERCs for the ecosystem....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-05</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-05.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-05.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS reached a major milestone by expanding documentation coverage to 95% while delivering critical stability fixes for the SQL plugin and a new unified interaction hook. The community is actively discussing specialized Solana trading architectures and resolving integration dependencies between Anthropic models and OpenAI embedding fallbacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;unified hooks with multi-transport support (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;add CachedDatabaseAdapter with LRU caching (draft)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Need to refresh for conversation to actually show as deleted (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical deep dive into Solana trading bot architecture involving GRPC ingesters and millisecond precision requirements. Resolution of Anthropic MCP integration issues regarding embedding fallbacks....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Focus on memory optimization for Turbo builds and progress on Eliza knowledge data pipelines. Security rotation of API keys was also performed....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-04</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-04.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-04.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS focused on architectural stability and developer experience, specifically through enhanced logging infrastructure and the introduction of experimental agent frameworks like roseOS. Meanwhile, the community addressed ongoing token migration issues and advanced Solana trading bot requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL Plugin Fix for SET LOCAL Parameterization (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;unified hooks with multi-transport support (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Need to refresh for conversation to actually show as deleted (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Focus on logging infrastructure through PR #6263 and troubleshooting severe memory leaks in the build process....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical deep dive into multi-model implementation and the requirement of GRPC ingesters for competitive Solana trading....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-03</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-03.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-03.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Development has shifted towards core performance optimizations, including a major refactor of the message service and infrastructure migration to the Jeju network. Concurrently, the community is managing a complex token migration while expanding the framework through experimental projects like roseOS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): use sql.raw() for SET LOCAL to avoid parameterization (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(default-message-service): optimize provider handling in MultiStep (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connect wallet action should lead directly to wallet options (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Focus on clearing the PR review queue and addressing a technical gap where singleShot functionality lacks parameter support....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#coders:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion on multi-model implementation using OpenRouter and deployment strategies for custom plugins in cloud containers....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#partners:&lt;/em&gt; Strategic exploration of 'Eliza DWS Transform,' an AI-powered agent to automate migration and cost reduction from AWS to the Jeju network....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2026-01-02</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-02.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-02.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Development has shifted significantly toward established strategic roadmaps for public agent ecosystems and gaming integrations, while persistent token migration issues for Tangem wallet users require community management attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;unified hooks with multi-transport support (HTTP/SSE/WebSocket) (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add an agent discovery module to the landing page and dashboard (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;v2.0.0 working branch (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Strategic shift towards building quality gaming experiences within hyperscape, specifically Zelda-like and RuneScape-inspired agent-integrated games....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Proposal for 'Eliza DWS Transform', an agent-based infrastructure tool to migrate SMB hosting from AWS to the Jeju network to reduce costs....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Community sentiment is high for the new year, though technical friction persists regarding token migration and wallet compatibility....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-31</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-01.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2026-01-01.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The community is navigating a transition to ElizaOS, focusing on the Jeju Network infrastructure and DegenAI trading framework. Technical progress is centered on backend integrations, image generation pipelines, and unified transport hooks for better developer experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;unified hooks with multi-transport support (HTTP/SSE/WebSocket) (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documentation expansion with Cloud integration (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;V2.0.0 Working Branch (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Focus on token utility, migration help, and the introduction of DegenAI as an autonomous trading framework powered by ElizaOS....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Technical discussions on Jeju backend, OAuth3 testnets, and speculative side projects like recreating classic games using the agent framework....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#partners:&lt;/em&gt; Market analysis revolving around debt monetization, capital rotation into risk-on assets, and infrastructure migration to self-owned data centers....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
