<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>elizaOS Daily Intelligence</title>
    <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge</link>
    <description>Daily facts and insights from the elizaOS ecosystem</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 02:31:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <ns0:link href="https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/rss/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-25</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-26.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-26.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion centered on the AI16Z→ElizaOS token migration, ongoing price decline, and exchange-support risk, while the team continued positioning Eliza Cloud as the primary near-term tokenomics/value-accrual mechanism. Development and roadmap work continued in parallel, including Cloud beta onboarding and upcoming mainnet milestones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snapshot Eligibility Issue + Tangem Wallet Connection Not Supported (Discord Support Compromised) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation focused on migration eligibility (Nov 11 snapshot wallet requirement), token mintability for Chainlink CCIP, migration rationale (moving off token2022 for exchange compatibility), token u...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Participants compared ElizaOS FDV (~$22M) to competitors (Pippin, Virtuals), discussed communication expectations, and reiterated that Cloud rollout is tied to implementing tokenomics....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Shaw proposed splitting Babylon into points and non-points components, with the points game using Eliza Cloud for inference/authentication and a stated target of migrating 350,000 users; discussion al...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-24</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-25.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-25.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Discussion centered on ElizaOS token value accrual and how Eliza Cloud revenue will be used, alongside near-term Cloud feature clarifications (upload limits, planned custom model hosting). Development updates emphasized documentation cleanup, plugin work (including Starknet), and CI reliability issues tied to Claude billing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monorepo documentation needs fixing (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Problems with spacing in numbered items (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conversation duplication bug (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opening agent chat should show most recent conversation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation focused on tokenomics and value accrual; team clarified that Eliza Cloud revenue (not yield) will be used for token buybacks, with further token utility planned for the Jeju release. Migr...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developer-focused discussion included plugin-starknet updates and guidance on building knowledge-backed agents in ElizaOS Cloud, including a 50MB upload limit, Markdown preference, and planned custom ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Debate on tokenomics compared ElizaOS to Virtual’s pairing model; team response emphasized token value tied to product usage and infrastructure development. Unusual sell patterns were discussed with s...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-23</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-24.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-24.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Eliza Cloud entered beta with ecosystem builders being onboarded ahead of a planned January ramp-up, while the team prepared for an 8004 mainnet milestone in mid-January and an agent onboarding push before EthDenver. In parallel, Discord discussions continued to center on ELIZAOS token utility/price concerns and near-term technical cleanup (plugin message standardization, analytics, and plugin fixes).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proposal to add a feedback button to the application. (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementation of chat renaming functionality. (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Addressing streaming and state management in the application. (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A request to update the Brandkit on GitHub. (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improves message service handlers to perform asynchronous operations and optimizes them for cloud platforms. (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Eliza Cloud was announced as entering beta with ecosystem builders being onboarded for production feedback; a January ramp-up plan (PR, launch event, coding influencers) and a mid-January 8004 mainnet...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core dev status updates included: a fix for streaming issues in cloud build mode, Discord plugin fixes, ongoing work on EPIC 5 items, a pending PR to standardize Elizaos.handleMessage across plugins, ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Brief discussion mentioned a community project (GAMEBORO, an AI gaming assistant on Steam) and shared metrics for elizaos and degenai....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-22</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-23.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-23.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community discussion centered on ELIZAOS token utility/price concerns alongside imminent product delivery, with the team emphasizing the near-term launch of Eliza Cloud and planned buybacks/airdrops. Technical threads focused on a Starknet plugin deployment error, interoperability strategy proposals, and a surfaced high-severity n8n RCE vulnerability reference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create Agent Button should be same in My Agents and Dashboard (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move avatar button to #4 in agent builder (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add Topics/Adjectives to form (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inline send message button (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tooltip for system prompt (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Token utility and price decline dominated, alongside repeated explanations that Eliza Cloud is near launch and that Cloud revenue will fund buybacks; ecosystem projects Babylon and Otako were cited as...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; A Starknet plugin 'unruggable' deployment flow failed with a String-to-BigInt parsing error; Odilitime requested the modified unruggable.ts for debugging. The suspended main X account and alternate ac...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; A brief market-structure note stated there are more sellers than buyers and referenced weak AI-crypto sector performance as context for price action....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-20</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-22.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-22.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community discussion centered on token price performance and ongoing ai16z→elizaOS migration constraints, while the team prepared to ship an ElizaOS Cloud MVP with streaming capabilities. Parallel GitHub work emphasized stability (migrations, security fixes), streaming foundations, plugin ecosystem expansion, and UX/onboarding planning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): optimize pre-1.6.5 migration, RLS handling and SQL organisation (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: encryption for character secrets in correct order (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Add ElizaOS Cloud as Default AI Provider in CLI (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add self-hosted Farcaster plugin to registry (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement unified messaging API (plugin-telegram) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#elizaos:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion included concerns about elizaOS token price behavior, confusion about ai16z→elizaOS migration (including eligibility constraints), confirmation of a signed X (Twitter) deal, and product upd...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#elizaos:&lt;/em&gt; Migration deadline details (Feb 4, 2026) were reiterated, with clarification that ai16z is tradable but has no utility and elizaOS is the supported path. Technical coordination for cloud streaming was...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-20</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-21.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-21.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community focus centered on ElizaOS token price weakness and ongoing AI16Z→ELIZAOS migration confusion, alongside heightened scam/impersonation risk. The team signaled near-term product momentum (Cloud MVP shipping Monday, v1.7.0 streaming release) and a business milestone (deal signed with X), with promises of token utility and buybacks plus a Q1/Q2 2026 roadmap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The SQL plugin was enhanced to ensure smooth data migration for users updating from older versions (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A test failure in the CLI was resolved to improve reliability of the development environment (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI improvements to make plugin selection more intuitive (toggle selection / visual feedback) (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UI improvements to make plugin selection more intuitive (toggle selection / visual feedback) (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redesigned dashboard planning (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Dominant themes were token price decline, confusion/anger around the AI16Z→ELIZAOS migration (including AI16Z pumping despite deprecation), and repeated scam-link warnings. A team member indicated Clo...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Brief updates/links highlighted the v1.7.0 release (streaming + npm fixes), discussion comparing the tool to Playwright/Puppeteer (embedded approach), request for TradingView chart integration, and mi...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Only a single post sharing the v1.7.0 GitHub release link; no discussion....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-19</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-20.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-20.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Primary themes were continued community friction around the AI16Z→elizaOS token migration (deadline set for 2026-02-04) and a near-term engineering push to ship cloud streaming, alongside ongoing work on EVM/onchain capabilities and ecosystem analytics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: bootstrap action/provide format change fix + initPromise fix (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize Agent Builder Model Selection (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow JSON export without deploying (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rename chat assistant to "Agent Builder" (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix markdown bullet point rendering (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation was dominated by token migration status and sentiment: elizaOS positioned as the only utility-forward token, AI16Z still tradable but without utility, and a firm migration deadline of 202...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developers discussed onchain/EVM support maturity: concerns about plugin-evm maintenance, ongoing EVM support work for Spartan, and an updated “knowledge repository” exposing JSON endpoints (leaderboa...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core team outlined release sequencing for cloud streaming: release monorepo → review/merge elizacloud-plugin → update cloud-v2 to latest core. They also noted NPM token changes breaking releases (clas...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-18</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-19.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-19.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Engineering effort centered on improving agent messaging/streaming and provider performance (parallelization + timeouts), while ecosystem work highlighted Starknet plugin integration breakages. Community discourse was dominated by token migration/exchange confusion and negative sentiment over price/perceived delivery gaps, alongside a notable Hyperfy v0.16.0 release announcement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: enhance streaming support in text generation (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;refactor(default-message-service): optimize provider handling in MultiStep (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: bootstrap action/provide format change fix + initPromise fix (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;remove reassign runtime.db to individual connection (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docs (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation was dominated by negative community sentiment: complaints about token price decline, perceived lack of product delivery, and a contentious AI16Z→ELIZAOS migration described as confusing/d...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Starknet plugin integration troubleshooting: questions on correct plugin installation approach, widespread TypeScript type mismatches (AgentRuntime vs IAgentRuntime) across action files, and a runtime...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core discussion centered on provider performance architecture: PR #6263 proposes parallel provider execution with configurable timeout (default 1s) and warnings for slow providers, with debate on enfo...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-17</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-18.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-18.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Primary themes were continued friction and confusion around the AI16Z→ELIZAOS migration (especially exchange-specific handling and Korean community concerns), alongside ongoing core product work (streaming, plugin actions) and process pressure to merge an oversized Discord plugin PR. GitHub signals strong near-term prioritization of UI/UX simplification (terminology cleanups, edit-mode behavior fixes) and platform stability work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix edit mode chat suggestions triggering agent responses (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix avatar mismatch between edit view and sidebar (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Replace "RAG" terminology with plain language (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snapshot Eligibility Issue + Tangem Wallet Connection Not Supported (Discord Support Compromised) (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Conversation was dominated by token migration confusion and frustration (notably Korean community concerns about Bithumb) and discrepancies in how exchanges (e.g., Bithumb vs Kraken) treat snapshot-ba...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developers discussed extending agent actions in a Starknet plugin context: suggested cloning the plugin into the monorepo packages folder, adding new action files under actions, and registering them v...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; A business/deployment signal emerged: market makers reportedly want agents deployed in production and visibly engaging in social environments before committing further; emphasis was placed on iteratin...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-16</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-17.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-17.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community focus centered on token migration logistics and credibility signals (Kraken listing on Dec 19; migration delays and a reported migration-site compromise), alongside steady engineering progress on cloud enablement, authentication, and developer workflow automation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Unified API - serverless - nodejs (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): migrate to messageService API and auto-create PGLite directories (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Add ElizaOS Cloud as Default AI Provider in CLI (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Primary discussion centered on AI16Z→ElizaOS migration mechanics and a key credibility catalyst: Kraken listing scheduled for Dec 19 with a 1:6 distribution ratio for Nov 11 snapshot holders. Communit...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Two parallel engineering threads: (1) a Polymarket tracking agent was built, writing bets into Neon and deployed to GitHub and Fly.io (next step: tighten conversational behavior), and (2) persistent l...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Core developers compared AI-assisted development workflows (Cursor Opus, multi-instance prompting across machines), discussed virtualization/worktree/container strategies to manage parallel AI session...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-15</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-16.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-16.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community attention centered on AI16Z→ElizaOS token migration friction (notably Bithumb delays) and an urgent, unverified claim that the migration site was compromised and used to drain tokens. In parallel, engineering discussions emphasized cloud-platform rollout and quality/stability improvements (SQL fixes, auth foundations, and tighter PR validation expectations).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Unified API - serverless - nodejs (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;.eliza needed or plugin-sql crashes, should autocreate (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docs (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Primary thread: token migration delays (especially Bithumb/Korean users) and responsibility clarification (CEX-held tokens must be migrated by exchanges). A high-risk allegation emerged that the migra...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Engineering support focused on a DB failure mode where Twitter replies triggered foreign key constraint errors; a contributor suggested latest codebase includes SQL fixes. Additional help centered on ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Proposal to repurpose the partners channel into an 'Eliza-Alpha' preview channel for cloud demos/teasers, inviting strategic non-holders to test and amplify (especially if X access returns). A core me...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-14</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-15.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-15.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; elizaOS discussions centered on accelerating Eliza Cloud toward a full create→publish→monetize→promote loop (with SEO, ads, and social publishing integrations) while users surfaced practical friction around token migration via hardware wallets and plugin/config errors. GitHub activity (month-to-date) indicates heavy platform hardening plus major platform-enabling workstreams (cloud integration, unified API, and JWT-based multi-tenant auth).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Unified API - serverless - nodejs (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;.eliza needed or plugin-sql crashes, should autocreate (closed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Shaw reported Eliza Cloud is progressing toward rapid building of agents/apps/n8n workflows and MCP/A2A services, explicitly implementing a business loop (create→publish→monetize→promote) with new SEO...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users discussed migrating Ai16z tokens to ElizaOS using Ledger hardware wallets; a recurring issue is holdings not appearing when connecting Ledger directly. Community guidance recommends connecting L...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; A prior-day support thread indicates users encountered TEXT_LARGE errors even with minimal input; the likely cause was missing inference plugin registration (e.g., OpenAI), with outdated packages impl...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-13</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-14.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-14.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Community focus split between immediate developer UX issues (missing AI plugin causing TEXT_LARGE errors; plugin install failures likely due to outdated packages) and broader ecosystem concerns (token migration issues on Bithumb and price anxiety) alongside ongoing platform hardening and major feature work (Cloud integration, TypeScript/build stabilization, JWT auth/multi-tenant direction).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: resolve TypeScript build errors in every packages - first step (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: Add ElizaOS Cloud as Default AI Provider in CLI (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): migrate to messageService API and auto-create PGLite directories (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; A user reported TEXT_LARGE errors even for short prompts; root cause was identified as missing AI inference plugin registration (e.g., OpenAI). Follow-on OpenAI plugin install failures were attributed...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Mostly casual chat (memes/profile pictures) with minor product chatter: 'Kled app release' mentioned without details; a user suggested ElizaOS can interact with NFTs; brief MOCA reference; 'how to red...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; A brief mention of 'Business Eliza' suggests partner interest in a business-focused Eliza variant, but without implementation detail....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-13</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-13.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-13.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS community focused heavily on prediction markets and price betting mechanisms while developers addressed critical security vulnerabilities and implemented major authentication improvements. Technical discussions centered around hackathon opportunities and integration challenges with various APIs and payment systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users initiated prediction markets for ElizaOS token price betting, with DorianD proposing bets on whether ElizaOS would be above/below $0.01 by NYE. Discussion included time decay algorithms for bett...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical discussions focused on Twitter agent API consumption issues, data pipeline fixes for elizaOS/knowledge repository, and guidance on integrating x402 payment capabilities. Users also discussed...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Brief technical discussions about workflow alerts, security agent development sprint planning, and suggestions to reduce GitHub Discord webhook noise by filtering to important events only....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-11</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-12.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-12.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The day's intelligence is dominated by ElizaOS token migration issues, particularly affecting Korean users on Bithumb exchange, alongside core development progress including monorepo fixes and preparation for the Babylon web-based gaming platform launch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[DRAFT] feat(core): Implement parallel action execution in processActions (draft)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix: resolve TypeScript build errors in every packages - first step (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Significant frustration among Korean users regarding the ELIZA token migration on Bithumb exchange, with team members acknowledging issues but indicating they're waiting on Bithumb. Users expressed co...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Technical discussions focused on ElizaOS deployment issues and integrations, particularly database connections (PGLite vs PostgreSQL), TypeScript build issues, and API integrations with Twitter and la...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Stan reported fixing critical issues in the monorepo (PR #6218) after Shaw's cleanup work broke types, tests, and try/catch blocks. Performance issues with pglite were noted (response times increasing...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-11</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-11.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-11.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; A critical security vulnerability was discovered in elizaOS allowing attackers to extract secrets via API endpoints, while ongoing plugin issues with SQL and Twitter components continue to affect users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eliza Cloud Integration, add MCP + A2A service starter, integrate CLI and starter projects tight (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(plugin-sql): optimize pre-1.6.5 migration, RLS handling and SQL organisation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; A critical security vulnerability was discovered where server doesn't require ELIZA_SERVER_AUTH_TOKEN, allowing attackers to extract secrets via API endpoints. The issue stems from process.env being d...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Multiple users reported foreign key constraint errors with plugin-sql and plugin-twitter components when creating memories. Stan is working on a fix and migration guide. Users also discussed API optio...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; Discussion focused on Polymarket's marketing strategy using a 50 Cent song, targeting sports bettors and users who might identify with government scrutiny....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-10</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-10.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-10.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The ElizaOS ecosystem faces significant user frustration around the AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration process while development teams focus on code quality improvements and upcoming projects like ElizaOS Cloud, Babylon, and Jeju.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaw/chore/deslop (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[DRAFT] feat(core): Implement parallel action execution in processActions (draft)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: enhance streaming support in text generation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Community members expressed significant frustration about the AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration process, which involved a sudden snapshot that caught holders off-guard. The token price is declining des...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Technical discussions focused on code quality improvements with Shaw submitting PR #6213 to fix types, remove unnecessary try/catch blocks, and clean up code. Future plans mentioned for "jeju" project...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Brief discussions about monetizing LLM models with x402 and Ollama, plus mentions of ROFL (Rust Optimized Fast Ledger) as potential technology for payment verification. Alchemy.com was recommended as ...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-09</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-09.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-09.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; A critical security breach on the elizaOS.ai website was resolved, while development continues on significant features including parallel action execution, streaming functionality, and JWT authentication, amid user concerns about Twitter agent limitations and token price decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[DRAFT] feat(core): Implement parallel action execution in processActions (draft)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: enhance streaming support in text generation (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: bump deps, fix drizzle-kit across ecosystem (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users expressed frustration about the ElizaOS token's continuous downtrend (approximately 40% in a month) while other cryptocurrencies recover. Significant discussion about Twitter agent functionality...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Brief technical discussions about extending PostgreSQL databases to work with ElizaOS's SQL plugin needs, with a GitHub code reference provided. A user also asked for recommendations on plugins to fet...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; A critical security incident was discovered and resolved where the elizaOS.ai website was compromised with an XMR cryptocurrency miner due to outdated Next.js dependencies with known RCE vulnerabiliti...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-08</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-08.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-08.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Development continues on core ElizaOS features including JWT authentication and parallel action execution, while users experience ongoing issues with the ai16z to ElizaOS token migration process that has prompted confusion and requests for clearer guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat(auth): implement JWT authentication and user management (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[DRAFT] feat(core): Implement parallel action execution in processActions (draft)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;feat: bump deps, fix drizzle-kit across ecosystem (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;.eliza needed or plugin-sql crashes, should autocreate (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users continue experiencing issues with the ai16z to ElizaOS token migration process, with many reporting that their tokens aren't showing as eligible in the portal. Community members are directing us...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#💬-coders:&lt;/em&gt; Developer questions about implementing custom REST API endpoints in ElizaOS projects remained unanswered. A new developer with Sui ecosystem and Move language experience introduced themselves to the c...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;#core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; GitHub pull request #6210 was shared in the channel, though no technical details were discussed....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>elizaOS Intelligence: 2025-12-07</title>
      <link>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-07.json</link>
      <guid>https://elizaos.github.io/knowledge/the-council/facts/2025-12-07.json</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; ElizaOS continues token migration from AI16Z with user confusion and technical issues reported, while development progresses on ElizaCloud and parallel action execution architecture (PR #6209), alongside a new decentralized OTC desk announcement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[DRAFT] feat(core): Implement parallel action execution in processActions (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add ElizaOS Cloud as Default AI Provider in CLI (merged)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fix(cli): correct startAgents API signature in e2e-tests (open)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;💬-discussion:&lt;/em&gt; Users continue to experience confusion about the AI16Z to ElizaOS token migration process, with technical issues including 'Max Amount Reached' errors. Terminological debates about 'hard fork vs. migr...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;🥇-partners:&lt;/em&gt; ElizaCloud release timeline was discussed with only a vague 'soon(tm)' response provided. A user suggested designing products with power users in mind, as most revenue will come from highly engaged us...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;core-devs:&lt;/em&gt; Developers discussed a draft PR (#6209) for implementing parallel execution of actions, which would optimize processing time while maintaining the integrity of dependent action sequences....&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
